1
00:05:00,676 --> 00:05:05,221
Bio-readouts are in the green.
Looks like she's alive.

2
00:05:07,725 --> 00:05:10,727
There goes our salvage.

3
00:05:37,254 --> 00:05:40,298
- How are we today?
- Terrible.

4
00:05:40,466 --> 00:05:44,511
- Better than yesterday, at least.
- Where am l?

5
00:05:44,678 --> 00:05:48,556
You're safe. You're at Gateway Station,
been here two days.

6
00:05:48,724 --> 00:05:52,268
You were pretty groggy at first,
but now you're OK.

7
00:05:52,436 --> 00:05:55,188
Looks like you've got a visitor.

8
00:05:56,690 --> 00:05:58,942
Jonesy. Come here.

9
00:06:00,110 --> 00:06:02,111
Come here.

10
00:06:02,279 --> 00:06:07,534
How are you, you stupid cat?
Where have you been?

11
00:06:08,577 --> 00:06:12,413
I guess you two have met.
I'm Carter Burke.

12
00:06:12,581 --> 00:06:18,461
I work for the company.
But don't let that fool you. I'm an OK guy.

13
00:06:18,629 --> 00:06:24,133
I'm glad you're a little better. The weakness
and disorientation should pass soon.

14
00:06:24,301 --> 00:06:30,098
It's just natural side effects
of such an unusually long hyper sleep.

15
00:06:30,266 --> 00:06:34,811
What do you mean?
How long was I out there?

16
00:06:37,106 --> 00:06:40,149
Has no one discussed this with you yet?

17
00:06:40,317 --> 00:06:44,821
But, l mean, I don't recognize this place.

18
00:06:45,656 --> 00:06:48,157
No, I know.

19
00:06:48,325 --> 00:06:51,828
It's just that this might be a shock.
It's longer...

20
00:06:51,996 --> 00:06:55,164
How long? Please.

21
00:06:57,251 --> 00:06:59,502
57 years.

22
00:07:00,212 --> 00:07:04,424
- What?
- You were out there for 57 years.

23
00:07:05,467 --> 00:07:08,678
You had drifted
right through the core systems,

24
00:07:08,846 --> 00:07:14,684
and it's really just blind luck
that a deep-salvage team found you.

25
00:07:14,852 --> 00:07:19,355
It's one in a thousand, really.
You're damn lucky to be alive, kiddo.

26
00:07:19,523 --> 00:07:23,026
You could be floating out there forever.

27
00:07:23,193 --> 00:07:36,873
Are you OK?

28
00:07:45,549 --> 00:07:47,550
God!

29
00:07:48,260 --> 00:07:50,219
Nurse!

30
00:07:51,513 --> 00:07:54,265
Someone get in here now.

31
00:07:54,767 --> 00:07:56,392
Now!

32
00:07:56,560 --> 00:07:58,728
- Hold.
- Please...

33
00:07:59,271 --> 00:08:01,022
Hold her.

34
00:08:01,732 --> 00:08:04,233
Kill me!

35
00:08:20,542 --> 00:08:25,421
Bad dreams again?
Want something to help you sleep?

36
00:08:26,090 --> 00:08:28,007
I've slept enough.

37
00:08:32,346 --> 00:08:34,055
Come here.

38
00:08:40,562 --> 00:08:42,563
It's all right.

39
00:08:47,569 --> 00:08:49,445
It's over.

40
00:09:14,888 --> 00:09:20,226
- Sorry I'm late.
- Is there any word about my daughter?

41
00:09:20,394 --> 00:09:24,981
I think we should worry about the hearing
now, cos we don't have long.

42
00:09:25,149 --> 00:09:29,152
I read your deposition, and it's great.
Stick to that and we'll be fine.

43
00:09:29,319 --> 00:09:31,988
There'll be a lot of heavyweights there -

44
00:09:32,156 --> 00:09:37,493
feds, Interstellar Commerce Commission,
Colonial Administration, insurance guys...

45
00:09:37,661 --> 00:09:40,329
Do you have any news
about my daughter?

46
00:09:41,874 --> 00:09:46,002
We did come up with some information.
Why don't we sit down?

47
00:09:46,170 --> 00:09:50,173
I was hoping to wait
until after the inquest...

48
00:09:53,177 --> 00:09:59,682
Amanda Ripley-McClaren -
married name, I guess - aged 66.

49
00:09:59,850 --> 00:10:03,269
And that was at the time of her death.

50
00:10:03,437 --> 00:10:06,314
Which was two years ago.

51
00:10:07,858 --> 00:10:10,151
I'm real sorry.

52
00:10:20,037 --> 00:10:22,121
Amy...

53
00:10:23,832 --> 00:10:28,544
She was interred at Westlake Repository,
Little Chute, Wisconsin.

54
00:10:28,712 --> 00:10:31,422
No children. I checked.

55
00:10:36,011 --> 00:10:40,806
I promised her
that I'd be home for her birthday.

56
00:10:44,144 --> 00:10:46,896
Her 11th birthday.

57
00:10:57,908 --> 00:11:00,076
I don't understand this.

58
00:11:00,244 --> 00:11:03,412
We have been here
for three and a half hours.

59
00:11:03,580 --> 00:11:06,290
How many different ways
do you want me to tell the same story?

60
00:11:07,251 --> 00:11:11,045
Look at it from our perspective, please.

61
00:11:11,213 --> 00:11:13,256
Please.

62
00:11:15,592 --> 00:11:20,930
You admit to destroying
an M-Class star-freighter,

63
00:11:21,098 --> 00:11:23,432
a rather expensive piece of hardware.

64
00:11:23,600 --> 00:11:29,605
42 million in adjusted dollars.
That's minus payload, of course.

65
00:11:29,773 --> 00:11:34,110
The lifeboat's flight recorder
corroborates some of your account,

66
00:11:34,278 --> 00:11:39,282
in that, for reasons unknown,
the Nostromo set down on LV-426,

67
00:11:39,449 --> 00:11:42,451
an unsurveyed planet at that time.

68
00:11:42,619 --> 00:11:47,373
That it resumed its course and was
subsequently set for self-destruct, by you,

69
00:11:47,541 --> 00:11:51,377
- for reasons unknown.
- Not for reasons unknown. I told you.

70
00:11:51,545 --> 00:11:57,133
We landed there on company orders
to get this thing, which destroyed my crew.

71
00:11:57,301 --> 00:11:59,635
And your expensive ship.

72
00:11:59,803 --> 00:12:03,472
The analysis team,
which examined the lifeboat minutely,

73
00:12:03,640 --> 00:12:06,309
found no evidence of this creature.

74
00:12:06,476 --> 00:12:11,439
Good. That's because I blew it
out of the goddamn airlock.

75
00:12:12,482 --> 00:12:14,567
Like I said.

76
00:12:16,737 --> 00:12:20,823
Are there any species
like this hostile organism on LV-426?

77
00:12:20,991 --> 00:12:24,535
It's a rock. No indigenous life.

78
00:12:25,579 --> 00:12:28,998
Did IQs drop sharply while I was away?

79
00:12:29,166 --> 00:12:34,337
I said it was not indigenous.
It was a derelict spacecraft, an alien ship.

80
00:12:34,504 --> 00:12:39,008
It was not from there. Do you get it?
We homed in on its beacon.

81
00:12:39,176 --> 00:12:45,473
And found something never recorded once
in over 300 surveyed worlds.

82
00:12:45,641 --> 00:12:51,687
"A creature that gestates inside a living
human host." These are your words.

83
00:12:51,855 --> 00:12:56,525
- "And has concentrated acid for blood."
- That's right.

84
00:12:56,693 --> 00:13:03,199
I can see where this is going.
But I'm telling you that those things exist.

85
00:13:03,367 --> 00:13:06,494
- Thank you. That will be all.
- Please!

86
00:13:06,662 --> 00:13:08,829
Kane, the crew member...

87
00:13:08,997 --> 00:13:13,376
Kane, who went into that ship,
said he saw thousands of eggs there.

88
00:13:13,543 --> 00:13:17,213
- Thank you, that will be all.
- Goddammit, that's not all.

89
00:13:17,381 --> 00:13:20,007
If one of those things gets down here,

90
00:13:20,175 --> 00:13:25,721
you can kiss all of this bullshit goodbye!

91
00:13:32,979 --> 00:13:40,736
It is the finding of this court of inquiry
that Warrant Officer E Ripley, NOC 14472,

92
00:13:40,904 --> 00:13:44,198
has acted with questionable judgment,

93
00:13:44,366 --> 00:13:49,870
and is unfit to hold an ICC license
as a commercial flight officer.

94
00:13:50,038 --> 00:13:55,042
Said license is hereby
suspended indefinitely.

95
00:13:55,210 --> 00:14:01,799
No criminal charges will be filed, and you
are released on your own recognizance

96
00:14:01,967 --> 00:14:05,386
for a six-month period
of psychometric probation,

97
00:14:05,554 --> 00:14:11,100
to include monthly review
by an ICC psychiatric technician.

98
00:14:13,103 --> 00:14:15,020
These proceedings are closed.

99
00:14:26,032 --> 00:14:29,285
That could have been better.
Look, I think...

100
00:14:29,453 --> 00:14:31,579
Van Leuwen?

101
00:14:31,747 --> 00:14:35,082
Why don't you just check out LV-426?

102
00:14:35,250 --> 00:14:38,919
I don't have to.
There have been people there over 20 years,

103
00:14:39,087 --> 00:14:42,131
and they never mentioned
hostile organisms.

104
00:14:42,299 --> 00:14:45,176
- What people?
- Terraformers.

105
00:14:45,343 --> 00:14:50,973
Planet engineers. They set up big atmosphere
processors to make the air breathable.

106
00:14:51,141 --> 00:14:55,394
Takes decades. It's what we call
a “shake’n’bake” colony.

107
00:14:55,562 --> 00:14:59,106
How many colonists are there?

108
00:14:59,816 --> 00:15:03,652
60, maybe 70 families. Do you mind?

109
00:15:06,323 --> 00:15:08,449
Families.

110
00:15:10,786 --> 00:15:12,578
Jesus.

111
00:16:27,863 --> 00:16:33,158
- I'll be down in Maintenance, OK?
- Al?

112
00:16:33,326 --> 00:16:38,455
Remember you sent some wildcatters
out into the middle of nowhere last week?

113
00:16:38,623 --> 00:16:42,751
One of them's on the horn,
says he's onto something.

114
00:16:42,919 --> 00:16:46,380
- Wants to know if his claim will be honored.
- Why wouldn't it be?

115
00:16:46,548 --> 00:16:50,259
Because you sent them out there
on company orders maybe?

116
00:16:50,427 --> 00:16:55,431
Christ! Some honch in a cushy office
on Earth says go look at a grid reference.

117
00:16:55,599 --> 00:16:58,767
We look. They don't say why,
and I don't ask,

118
00:16:58,935 --> 00:17:01,729
because it takes two weeks
to get an answer,

119
00:17:01,897 --> 00:17:04,231
and the answer is always "Don't ask."

120
00:17:04,399 --> 00:17:06,483
So what do I tell this guy?

121
00:17:06,651 --> 00:17:10,487
As far as I'm concerned,
if he finds something, it is his.

122
00:17:10,655 --> 00:17:13,115
- Lydecker?
- What?

123
00:17:13,283 --> 00:17:18,329
You kids know you're not supposed
to be on this level. Get outta here.

124
00:17:49,069 --> 00:17:54,323
- You go in places we can't fit.
- That's why I'm the best.

125
00:17:54,491 --> 00:17:59,119
Knock it off. I catch you playing
in the air ducts again, I'll tan your hides.

126
00:17:59,287 --> 00:18:01,497
- All the kids...
- I don't care.

127
00:18:01,665 --> 00:18:04,124
Wait a minute. Annie, look at this.

128
00:18:14,844 --> 00:18:17,846
Folks, we have scored big this time.

129
00:18:24,521 --> 00:18:26,855
What is it, Dad?

130
00:18:30,402 --> 00:18:37,199
I'm not sure. Let's try and get a closer look
at it through that crack down the side.

131
00:18:37,367 --> 00:18:41,495
- Shouldn't we call in?
- Let's wait till we know what to call it in as.

132
00:18:45,959 --> 00:18:51,380
That's about as close as we can get.
Shall we take a look inside?

133
00:19:06,312 --> 00:19:09,398
You kids stay inside.
We'll be right back.

134
00:19:09,566 --> 00:19:11,567
OK. Bye.

135
00:20:29,521 --> 00:20:32,648
Timmy, they've been gone a long time.

136
00:20:32,816 --> 00:20:35,943
It'll be OK, Newt.
Dad knows what he's doing.

137
00:20:37,237 --> 00:20:44,118
Mayday! This is Alpha Kilo
Two Four Nine calling Hadley Control!

138
00:21:30,081 --> 00:21:35,502
Hi, Ripley. This is Lieutenant Gorman
of the Colonial Marine Corps...

139
00:21:35,670 --> 00:21:37,880
We have to talk.

140
00:21:38,047 --> 00:21:41,967
We've lost contact
with the colony on LV-426.

141
00:21:48,224 --> 00:21:50,392
I don't believe this.

142
00:21:50,560 --> 00:21:55,063
You throw me at the wolves,
and now you want me to go back out there?

143
00:21:55,231 --> 00:21:57,816
Forget it. It's not my problem.

144
00:21:57,984 --> 00:22:01,361
- Can I finish?
- There's no way.

145
00:22:02,864 --> 00:22:07,534
You wouldn't be going in with the troops.
I guarantee your safety.

146
00:22:07,702 --> 00:22:10,746
These Colonial Marines
are very tough hombres.

147
00:22:10,914 --> 00:22:15,375
They pack state-of-the-art firepower.
There's nothing they can't handle.

148
00:22:15,627 --> 00:22:20,255
- Lieutenant, am I right?
- We're trained to deal with these situations.

149
00:22:20,423 --> 00:22:22,341
Then you don't need me.
I'm not a soldier.

150
00:22:23,968 --> 00:22:26,428
We don't know
what's going on out there.

151
00:22:26,596 --> 00:22:30,599
It may just be a downed transmitter, okay?
But if it's not,

152
00:22:30,767 --> 00:22:34,770
I would like you there as an adviser,
and that's all.

153
00:22:37,941 --> 00:22:41,944
What's your interest in this?
Why are you going?

154
00:22:42,111 --> 00:22:46,406
The corporation co-financed that colony
with Colonial Administration.

155
00:22:46,574 --> 00:22:49,785
We're into a lot of terraforming,
building better worlds...

156
00:22:49,953 --> 00:22:55,040
Yeah, I saw the commercial.
I've gotta get to work.

157
00:22:56,167 --> 00:22:59,086
I heard you're working
in the cargo docks.

158
00:22:59,253 --> 00:23:00,295
That's right.

159
00:23:00,463 --> 00:23:03,131
- Running forklifts?
- So?

160
00:23:03,299 --> 00:23:06,426
Nothing. It's great
that you're keeping busy.

161
00:23:06,594 --> 00:23:12,057
And I know it's the only thing you
could get. There's nothing wrong with it.

162
00:23:14,143 --> 00:23:18,063
What if I told you I could
get you reinstated as a flight officer?

163
00:23:18,231 --> 00:23:22,067
The company's agreed
to pick up your contract.

164
00:23:22,235 --> 00:23:24,277
If I go.

165
00:23:25,321 --> 00:23:29,116
If you go. Come on.
That's a second chance, kiddo.

166
00:23:29,283 --> 00:23:34,162
I think for you it would be best
to face this thing, get back on the horse...

167
00:23:34,330 --> 00:23:37,332
Spare me. I've had
my psych evaluation this month.

168
00:23:37,500 --> 00:23:41,503
I know. l read it. You wake up every night
soaking with sweat...

169
00:23:41,671 --> 00:23:43,839
I said no, and I mean it.

170
00:23:46,801 --> 00:23:53,015
Now please leave. I am not going back,
and I would be no good to you if I did.

171
00:23:53,474 --> 00:23:55,100
OK.

172
00:23:57,520 --> 00:24:01,023
Would you do me a favor?
Just think about it.

173
00:24:04,027 --> 00:24:06,319
Thanks for the coffee.

174
00:25:14,305 --> 00:25:16,348
Hello?

175
00:25:19,102 --> 00:25:22,604
- You OK?
- Just tell me one thing.

176
00:25:22,772 --> 00:25:25,941
You're going out there
to destroy them, right?

177
00:25:26,109 --> 00:25:31,071
Not to study, not to bring back,
but to wipe them out.

178
00:25:32,198 --> 00:25:35,117
That's the plan. You have my word on it.

179
00:25:37,787 --> 00:25:39,621
All right, I'm in.

180
00:25:49,090 --> 00:25:51,424
And you, you little shithead,

181
00:25:52,969 --> 00:25:55,846
you're staying here.

182
00:28:26,455 --> 00:28:30,375
They ain't payin' us enough for this, man.

183
00:28:30,543 --> 00:28:33,420
Not enough to have to
wake up to your face, Drake.

184
00:28:33,587 --> 00:28:34,629
What?

185
00:28:34,880 --> 00:28:35,964
Is that a joke?

186
00:28:36,132 --> 00:28:38,258
I wish it were.

187
00:28:38,426 --> 00:28:43,263
Hey, Hicks. You look just like I feel.

188
00:28:45,433 --> 00:28:48,768
OK, sweethearts, what are you waiting for?
Breakfast in bed?

189
00:28:48,936 --> 00:28:54,107
Another glorious day in the Corps. A day in
the Marine Corps is like a day on the farm.

190
00:28:54,275 --> 00:28:59,029
Every meal's a banquet, every paycheck
a fortune, every formation a parade.

191
00:28:59,196 --> 00:29:03,199
- I love the Corps.
- This floor is freezing.

192
00:29:03,367 --> 00:29:07,829
- Want me to fetch your slippers for you?
- Gee, would you, sir?

193
00:29:07,997 --> 00:29:12,834
Look into my eye.
Fall in, people. Let's go.

194
00:29:13,002 --> 00:29:16,838
- I hate this job.
- Crowe, Wierzbowski, on your feet.

195
00:29:17,006 --> 00:29:19,716
You just had three weeks on your back.

196
00:29:19,884 --> 00:29:22,969
I'm talkin' about breathing,
not this frozen shit.

197
00:29:23,137 --> 00:29:25,680
Yeah, Top, how about it?

198
00:29:28,559 --> 00:29:32,687
First assembly's in 1 5, people. Shag it.

199
00:29:33,981 --> 00:29:36,566
Who's Snow White?

200
00:29:37,443 --> 00:29:42,363
She's some kind of consultant.
Apparently she saw an alien once.

201
00:29:42,531 --> 00:29:45,533
Whoopee-fucking-do. I'm impressed.

202
00:29:50,039 --> 00:29:54,167
Vasquez, have you
ever been mistaken for a man?

203
00:29:54,335 --> 00:29:56,294
No. Have you?

204
00:30:00,216 --> 00:30:03,510
You're just too bad.

205
00:30:11,894 --> 00:30:16,856
- Top, what's the op?
- It's a rescue mission. You'll love it.

206
00:30:17,024 --> 00:30:22,278
There's some juicy colonists' daughters
we have to rescue from their virginity.

207
00:30:22,446 --> 00:30:25,156
Dumb-ass colonists.

208
00:30:27,576 --> 00:30:31,246
- What's this crap supposed to be?
- Corn bread, I think.

209
00:30:31,413 --> 00:30:34,249
It's good for you, boy. Eat it.

210
00:30:34,416 --> 00:30:38,586
I sure wouldn't mind gettin' some
more Arcturian poontang. Remember?

211
00:30:38,754 --> 00:30:44,092
- Yeah, Frost, but your one was male.
- Doesn't matter when it's Arcturian.

212
00:30:44,260 --> 00:30:47,053
- Bishop, do the thing with the knife.
- Oh, please.

213
00:30:47,221 --> 00:30:49,305
Come on.

214
00:30:49,473 --> 00:30:53,143
- All right!
- I don't wanna see that.

215
00:30:55,771 --> 00:31:01,943
What are you doin'?
Quit messin' around, Drake. Bishop!

216
00:31:02,444 --> 00:31:04,112
- Do it.
- Not me, man!

217
00:31:04,280 --> 00:31:06,614
- Yeah, you.
- Quit messin' around.

218
00:31:06,782 --> 00:31:08,867
Trust me.

219
00:31:22,256 --> 00:31:25,800
- All right, knock it off.
- Thank you.

220
00:31:29,180 --> 00:31:33,099
- Enjoy your meal.
- That wasn't funny.

221
00:31:36,478 --> 00:31:39,814
- Lieutenant Gorman? Mr. Burke?
- Thanks.

222
00:31:40,691 --> 00:31:46,362
Looks like the new lieutenant's
too good to eat with the rest of us grunts.

223
00:31:46,530 --> 00:31:49,657
The boy's got a corncob up his ass.

224
00:31:51,160 --> 00:31:54,996
Thought you never missed.

225
00:31:56,790 --> 00:32:01,294
You said nothing about
an android being on board. Why not?

226
00:32:01,462 --> 00:32:06,716
It never occurred to me.
We always have a synthetic on board.

227
00:32:06,884 --> 00:32:11,221
I prefer the term
"artificial person" myself.

228
00:32:11,388 --> 00:32:16,017
- Is there a problem?
- I'm sorry. I don't know why I didn't...

229
00:32:16,185 --> 00:32:20,813
Ripley's last trip out,
the artificial person malfunctioned.

230
00:32:20,981 --> 00:32:24,525
There were problems,
and a few deaths were involved.

231
00:32:24,693 --> 00:32:29,864
- I'm shocked. Was it an older model?
- The Hyperdyne Systems 120-A/2.

232
00:32:30,032 --> 00:32:33,159
That explains it.
The A/2s always were a bit twitchy.

233
00:32:33,327 --> 00:32:36,162
That can't happen
with our behavioural inhibitors.

234
00:32:36,330 --> 00:32:41,668
It is impossible for me to harm,
or allow to be harmed, a human being.

235
00:32:41,835 --> 00:32:44,462
Sure you don't want some?

236
00:32:45,047 --> 00:32:49,300
Just stay away from me.
You got that?

237
00:32:50,886 --> 00:32:53,680
Guess she don't like
the corn bread either.

238
00:33:07,194 --> 00:33:11,239
- Squad, atten-ho! Officer on deck.
- As you were.

239
00:33:11,407 --> 00:33:14,158
Quickly. Settle down.

240
00:33:14,326 --> 00:33:16,369
All right, listen up.

241
00:33:17,371 --> 00:33:22,417
Morning, Marines. Sorry we didn't have time
to brief you before we left Gateway...

242
00:33:22,584 --> 00:33:25,044
- Sir?
- What is it, Hicks?

243
00:33:25,587 --> 00:33:28,214
Hudson, sir. He's Hicks.

244
00:33:29,800 --> 00:33:33,386
- What's the question?
- Is this gonna be a stand-up fight,

245
00:33:33,554 --> 00:33:36,222
or another bug hunt?

246
00:33:36,390 --> 00:33:39,267
All we know is there's
no contact with the colony,

247
00:33:39,435 --> 00:33:42,186
and that a xenomorph may be involved.

248
00:33:42,354 --> 00:33:44,981
- A what?
- A xenomorph.

249
00:33:45,149 --> 00:33:47,275
It's a bug hunt.

250
00:33:47,443 --> 00:33:51,112
What exactly are we dealing with here?

251
00:33:52,072 --> 00:33:54,574
I'll tell you what I know.

252
00:33:54,742 --> 00:33:57,076
We set down on LV-426.

253
00:33:57,244 --> 00:33:59,620
A crew member
was brought back on board

254
00:33:59,788 --> 00:34:03,833
with something attached to his face,
some kind of parasite.

255
00:34:04,001 --> 00:34:09,213
We tried to get it off, but couldn't.
Later it seemed to come off by itself and die.

256
00:34:09,381 --> 00:34:14,135
Kane seemed fine.
We were all having dinner and...

257
00:34:14,303 --> 00:34:21,225
It must have laid something in his throat,
some sort of embryo. He started...

258
00:34:21,393 --> 00:34:27,482
I only need to know one thing:
where they are.

259
00:34:27,649 --> 00:34:30,360
- Go, Vasquez. Kick ass.
- Anytime, anywhere.

260
00:34:30,527 --> 00:34:35,156
Somebody said “alien”. She thought
they said “illegal alien” and signed up.

261
00:34:35,324 --> 00:34:37,950
- Fuck you.
- Anytime, anywhere.

262
00:34:38,118 --> 00:34:40,953
Are you finished?

263
00:34:45,167 --> 00:34:48,002
I hope you're right. l really do.

264
00:34:50,172 --> 00:34:56,344
OK, thank you, Ripley. We have Ripley's
report on disk. I suggest you study it.

265
00:34:56,512 --> 00:35:01,265
Because just one of those things wiped out
my entire crew in less than 24 hours.

266
00:35:01,433 --> 00:35:05,853
If the colonists found that ship, there's
no telling how many have been exposed.

267
00:35:06,021 --> 00:35:08,356
Do you understand?

268
00:35:10,943 --> 00:35:13,903
Anyway, we have it on disk,
so look at it.

269
00:35:14,071 --> 00:35:16,155
Any questions?

270
00:35:17,199 --> 00:35:21,661
- What is it, Private?
- How do I get out of this chickenshit outfit?

271
00:35:21,829 --> 00:35:24,539
You secure that shit, Hudson.

272
00:35:26,208 --> 00:35:28,209
All right.

273
00:35:28,377 --> 00:35:30,670
Now listen.

274
00:35:32,631 --> 00:35:37,343
I want this to go smooth,
and by the numbers.

275
00:35:37,511 --> 00:35:42,098
I want DCS and tactical
database assimilation by 0830.

276
00:35:42,266 --> 00:35:47,395
Ordnance loading, weapons strip and
dropship prep details will have seven hours.

277
00:35:47,563 --> 00:35:49,564
Now move it, people.

278
00:35:49,731 --> 00:35:53,943
You heard the man and you know the drill.
Assholes and elbows.

279
00:35:54,111 --> 00:35:56,654
Hudson, come here.

280
00:36:11,962 --> 00:36:14,755
I don't care if you are short.
Get it done.

281
00:36:14,923 --> 00:36:20,261
- You'll get lip cancer smokin' those.
- Corporal, I want this loading lock sealed.

282
00:36:20,429 --> 00:36:22,972
- How many more, Spunkmeyer?
- Last one.

283
00:36:23,140 --> 00:36:25,433
Take it away.

284
00:36:41,909 --> 00:36:44,202
Clear behind.

285
00:36:50,209 --> 00:36:52,877
Did you check number three?

286
00:36:53,045 --> 00:36:56,797
Hi. I feel like a fifth wheel.
Is there anything I can do?

287
00:36:56,965 --> 00:37:00,760
I don't know.
Is there anything you can do?

288
00:37:02,221 --> 00:37:05,431
I can drive that loader.

289
00:37:05,599 --> 00:37:10,436
- I have a Class 2 rating.
- Be my guest.

290
00:37:55,983 --> 00:37:58,651
Where you want it?

291
00:38:01,613 --> 00:38:03,322
Bay 1 2, please.

292
00:38:59,755 --> 00:39:03,257
All right. You're a team,
and there's nothing to worry about.

293
00:39:03,425 --> 00:39:08,387
We're gonna conquer,
and we're gonna kick some. Understood?

294
00:39:08,555 --> 00:39:12,266
That's what we're gonna do,
sweethearts.

295
00:39:12,434 --> 00:39:15,061
All right, people, on the ready line.

296
00:39:15,228 --> 00:39:16,562
Are you lean?

297
00:39:16,730 --> 00:39:18,064
Are you mean?

298
00:39:18,231 --> 00:39:20,733
- What are you?
- Lean, mean marines!

299
00:39:20,901 --> 00:39:25,279
Hudson! Get on the ready line.
Get some today!

300
00:39:25,447 --> 00:39:29,617
Get on the ready line!
Move it out, goddammit!

301
00:39:29,785 --> 00:39:33,162
Get hot! Get out, get out!

302
00:39:33,330 --> 00:39:36,040
Move it out, move it out!

303
00:39:41,296 --> 00:39:45,883
Absolutely badasses!
Let's pack 'em in. Get in there!

304
00:39:46,593 --> 00:39:48,344
Move it.

305
00:39:48,512 --> 00:39:54,141
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.

306
00:39:54,309 --> 00:39:58,604
I want combat seating.
You know your places.

307
00:39:58,772 --> 00:40:00,981
Get those weapons stowed.

308
00:40:01,149 --> 00:40:04,485
Come on, settle down, people.

309
00:40:05,946 --> 00:40:10,157
- Lock 'em in, Hudson.
- Ready to get it on? You know it.

310
00:40:10,742 --> 00:40:12,952
OK, Bishop, let's go.

311
00:40:13,453 --> 00:40:15,121
Roger.

312
00:40:16,957 --> 00:40:19,583
I'm ready, man.

313
00:40:19,751 --> 00:40:23,254
Ready to get it on.

314
00:40:27,718 --> 00:40:31,345
Cross-locking now.
Pre-launch auto cycle engaged.

315
00:40:34,683 --> 00:40:38,728
Primary couplers released.
Hit the internals.

316
00:40:51,032 --> 00:40:53,659
Confirm cross-lock
and drop stations secured.

317
00:40:53,827 --> 00:40:57,163
Affirmative. All drop stations secured.

318
00:41:00,834 --> 00:41:02,376
1 0 seconds.

319
00:41:06,006 --> 00:41:08,924
Stand by to initiate release sequencer.

320
00:41:09,092 --> 00:41:10,885
On my mark. Five...

321
00:41:11,052 --> 00:41:14,722
We're on an express elevator to hell.
Going down.

322
00:41:14,890 --> 00:41:17,892
..two, one, mark.

323
00:41:33,909 --> 00:41:36,160
Switch to DCS ranging.

324
00:41:36,328 --> 00:41:40,831
- 2-4-0. Nominal to profile.
- We're in the pipe. Five by five.

325
00:41:51,551 --> 00:41:55,221
- We're picking up some hull ionisation.
- Got it.

326
00:41:55,388 --> 00:41:58,599
Rough air ahead. We're in for some chop.

327
00:42:12,364 --> 00:42:16,784
How many drops is this for you,
Lieutenant?

328
00:42:16,952 --> 00:42:18,953
38.

329
00:42:20,038 --> 00:42:23,582
- Simulated.
- How many combat drops?

330
00:42:24,459 --> 00:42:27,753
Two. Including this one.

331
00:42:29,297 --> 00:42:31,131
- Shit.
- Oh, man.

332
00:42:44,354 --> 00:42:46,480
Range 014.

333
00:42:46,648 --> 00:42:49,149
Turning on final.

334
00:42:53,655 --> 00:42:57,241
- I got a bad feeling about this drop.
- You always say that.

335
00:42:57,409 --> 00:43:00,828
"l got a bad feeling about this drop."

336
00:43:00,996 --> 00:43:04,915
When we get back without ya,
I'll call your folks.

337
00:43:07,168 --> 00:43:11,338
All right. Let's see what we can see.

338
00:43:11,506 --> 00:43:14,383
Everybody online. Lookin' good.

339
00:43:16,511 --> 00:43:18,178
Drake, check your camera.

340
00:43:18,346 --> 00:43:20,180
There seems to be a malfunction.

341
00:43:20,432 --> 00:43:24,602
That's better. Pan it around a bit.
Good.

342
00:43:24,769 --> 00:43:26,896
I'm ready. Check it out.

343
00:43:27,063 --> 00:43:29,857
I am the ultimate badass.

344
00:43:30,025 --> 00:43:32,860
State-of-the-badass-art.

345
00:43:33,028 --> 00:43:35,529
You do not wanna fuck with me.

346
00:43:36,364 --> 00:43:38,699
Check it out.

347
00:43:39,701 --> 00:43:42,494
Ripley, don't worry.

348
00:43:42,662 --> 00:43:47,583
Me and my squad of ultimate badasses
will protect you.

349
00:43:47,751 --> 00:43:49,877
Check it out.

350
00:43:50,045 --> 00:43:53,547
Independently targeting
particle-beam Phalanx.

351
00:43:54,716 --> 00:43:57,343
Fry half a city with this puppy.

352
00:43:57,510 --> 00:44:02,556
We got tactical smart missiles,
phased-plasma pulse rifles, RPGs,

353
00:44:02,724 --> 00:44:05,726
we got sonic electronic ball breakers!

354
00:44:05,894 --> 00:44:09,229
We got nukes, we got knives,
sharp sticks...

355
00:44:09,397 --> 00:44:10,439
Knock it off.

356
00:44:10,607 --> 00:44:12,232
All right, gear up.

357
00:44:12,400 --> 00:44:17,821
Two minutes, people.
Somebody wake up Hicks.

358
00:44:31,419 --> 00:44:35,464
- Coming around for a 709.
- Terminal guidance locked in.

359
00:44:35,632 --> 00:44:37,758
Where's the damn beacon?

360
00:44:37,926 --> 00:44:40,177
Oh, I see it.

361
00:44:45,600 --> 00:44:48,852
- That's the atmosphere processor?
- That's it.

362
00:44:49,020 --> 00:44:52,231
Remarkable piece of machinery.
Completely automated.

363
00:44:52,399 --> 00:44:56,110
We manufacture those, by the way.

364
00:45:05,120 --> 00:45:09,707
Ferro, take us in low
over the main colony complex.

365
00:45:11,501 --> 00:45:15,629
Storm shutters are sealed.
There's no visible activity.

366
00:45:15,797 --> 00:45:17,381
Hold at 40.

367
00:45:17,632 --> 00:45:18,674
Roger.

368
00:45:18,842 --> 00:45:21,593
Give me a slow circle of the complex.

369
00:45:28,309 --> 00:45:30,728
Structure seems intact.

370
00:45:31,771 --> 00:45:36,984
- They still have power.
- Ferro, set down on the landing grid.

371
00:45:37,152 --> 00:45:39,820
Immediate dust-off on my clear,
then stay on station.

372
00:45:54,002 --> 00:45:56,336
Down and clear.

373
00:45:57,839 --> 00:46:00,758
Ten seconds, people. Look sharp.

374
00:46:02,719 --> 00:46:06,013
I want a nice clean dispersal this time.

375
00:46:08,183 --> 00:46:10,559
Let's go. Move it out.

376
00:46:10,727 --> 00:46:12,770
Head 'em up.

377
00:46:33,249 --> 00:46:37,002
First squad up online. Hicks, get yours
in a cordon. Watch the rear.

378
00:46:37,420 --> 00:46:40,380
Vasquez, take point. Let's move.

379
00:46:48,098 --> 00:46:50,224
Move up.

380
00:46:53,311 --> 00:46:55,896
Hudson, run a bypass.

381
00:47:00,735 --> 00:47:03,320
Second squad, move up.
Flanking positions.

382
00:47:03,488 --> 00:47:06,115
Second squad online.

383
00:47:34,269 --> 00:47:36,311
Are you set?

384
00:47:39,274 --> 00:47:41,358
Go on.

385
00:48:06,759 --> 00:48:11,805
Second team, move inside.
Hicks, take the upper level.

386
00:48:38,124 --> 00:48:42,669
Sir, are you copying this?
Looks like hits from small-arms fire.

387
00:48:42,837 --> 00:48:48,175
We got some explosives damage.
It's probably seismic survey charges.

388
00:48:48,343 --> 00:48:52,930
Are you readin' this?
Keep it tight, people.

389
00:49:05,485 --> 00:49:10,864
Hicks, Hudson,
use your motion trackers.

390
00:49:27,215 --> 00:49:29,925
Nothing. Not a goddamn thing.

391
00:49:36,182 --> 00:49:38,225
Quarter and search by twos.

392
00:49:50,238 --> 00:49:53,073
Dietrich, Frost, you're up.

393
00:50:39,787 --> 00:50:41,621
It's right in there.

394
00:50:54,135 --> 00:50:55,761
Now.

395
00:50:58,681 --> 00:51:03,643
- Good one, Hudson.
- Sir, we have a negative situation here.

396
00:51:03,811 --> 00:51:04,936
Moving on, sir.

397
00:51:14,405 --> 00:51:16,656
Wait. Tell him to...

398
00:51:17,825 --> 00:51:19,576
Back up.

399
00:51:19,744 --> 00:51:21,828
Pan right.

400
00:51:22,830 --> 00:51:24,664
There.

401
00:51:25,541 --> 00:51:28,376
You seein' this all right?

402
00:51:28,544 --> 00:51:34,091
Looks melted. Somebody must have bagged
one of Ripley's bad guys here.

403
00:51:34,258 --> 00:51:36,009
Acid for blood.

404
00:51:36,177 --> 00:51:39,679
If you like that, you're gonna love this.

405
00:51:52,944 --> 00:51:56,446
- Quit screwin' around.
- Second squad, what's your status?

406
00:51:56,614 --> 00:51:59,533
We've just finished our sweep.
Nobody's home.

407
00:51:59,700 --> 00:52:02,369
Roger. Sir, this place is dead.

408
00:52:02,537 --> 00:52:06,123
Whatever happened here,
I think we missed it.

409
00:52:06,290 --> 00:52:09,626
The area's secured.
Let's see what their computer can tell us.

410
00:52:09,794 --> 00:52:12,045
- It's not secured.
- The area is secured.

411
00:52:12,213 --> 00:52:15,132
First team, head for Operations.

412
00:52:15,383 --> 00:52:17,050
Hudson, try and get their CPU online.

413
00:52:17,218 --> 00:52:18,343
Affirmative.

414
00:52:18,511 --> 00:52:21,888
Hicks, meet me at the south lock.
We're coming in.

415
00:52:22,306 --> 00:52:27,394
- He's comin' in. I feel safer already.
- Pendejo jerk-off.

416
00:52:47,790 --> 00:52:51,459
Sir, we got the CPU online. No problem.

417
00:52:51,627 --> 00:52:54,212
Good. Stand by in Operations.

418
00:52:55,590 --> 00:52:57,257
OK, let's go.

419
00:53:18,154 --> 00:53:20,655
Are you all right?

420
00:53:38,799 --> 00:53:42,677
Sir, they sealed off this wing
at both ends.

421
00:53:42,845 --> 00:53:47,140
Welded the doors, and blocked off
the stairs with heavy equipment.

422
00:53:47,308 --> 00:53:50,310
But it looks like the barricade didn't hold.

423
00:53:50,478 --> 00:53:52,437
- Any bodies?
- No, sir.

424
00:53:52,605 --> 00:53:56,983
- Last stand.
- Must have been a hell of a fight.

425
00:53:57,151 --> 00:53:59,527
Looks that way.

426
00:54:01,614 --> 00:54:08,995
Drake, this way. We should be able
to cut through the medlab to Operations.

427
00:54:58,671 --> 00:55:00,755
Lieutenant.

428
00:55:21,819 --> 00:55:24,696
Are those the same ones?

429
00:55:36,250 --> 00:55:38,501
Careful.

430
00:55:47,970 --> 00:55:51,681
Looks like love at first sight to me.

431
00:55:51,849 --> 00:55:54,392
He likes you.

432
00:55:54,560 --> 00:55:57,854
Two are alive, the rest are dead.

433
00:55:58,773 --> 00:56:01,733
Surgically removed
before embryo implantation.

434
00:56:01,901 --> 00:56:06,571
Subject: Marachuk, John J.
Died during the procedure.

435
00:56:06,739 --> 00:56:08,907
They killed him taking it off.

436
00:56:13,746 --> 00:56:16,331
I think we got something here.

437
00:56:20,920 --> 00:56:23,963
- Behind us.
- One of us?

438
00:56:24,131 --> 00:56:27,300
Apone, where are your people?
Anybody in D-Block?

439
00:56:27,468 --> 00:56:31,262
Negative. We're all in Operations.

440
00:56:33,432 --> 00:56:35,517
Talk to me, Frosty.

441
00:56:35,684 --> 00:56:38,186
Just keep movin', baby.

442
00:56:55,913 --> 00:56:58,039
- It's moving.
- Which way?

443
00:56:58,207 --> 00:57:01,793
It's coming straight for us. Straight up.

444
00:57:39,290 --> 00:57:41,457
- Fuck.
- Hold up.

445
00:58:05,399 --> 00:58:07,650
It's all right. Come on.

446
00:58:07,818 --> 00:58:12,197
- Just grab her, Corporal.
- Don't be afraid. We won't hurt you.

447
00:58:12,865 --> 00:58:15,909
It's all right. Come on out.

448
00:58:16,076 --> 00:58:17,994
Come on. Easy...

449
00:58:18,162 --> 00:58:19,412
I got her.

450
00:58:19,580 --> 00:58:21,122
Damn!

451
00:58:21,290 --> 00:58:23,833
- Don't let her go.
- She's under the grille.

452
00:58:24,001 --> 00:58:28,421
- Frost, get your light up here.
- Where'd she go?

453
00:58:30,174 --> 00:58:32,967
- Shine the light.
- Down here.

454
00:58:34,053 --> 00:58:36,387
- Here.
- There she is.

455
00:58:36,555 --> 00:58:38,431
Keep back. Don't scare her.

456
00:58:38,599 --> 00:58:42,101
- Grab her. We're gonna lose her.
- Damn it.

457
00:58:48,234 --> 00:58:50,318
Wait.

458
00:59:15,427 --> 00:59:18,304
It's OK. It's all right.

459
00:59:19,848 --> 00:59:22,141
Don't be afraid.

460
00:59:23,143 --> 00:59:25,186
See?

461
00:59:25,354 --> 00:59:27,272
Wait. No, you don't.

462
00:59:27,815 --> 00:59:31,150
It's OK. You're gonna be all right now.

463
00:59:33,654 --> 00:59:37,073
Easy, easy. It's gonna be OK.

464
00:59:37,241 --> 00:59:39,909
You're gonna be OK.

465
00:59:42,037 --> 00:59:44,956
Easy, easy.

466
01:00:21,452 --> 01:00:23,995
- What's her name again?
- Rebecca.

467
01:00:24,163 --> 01:00:27,832
Think, Rebecca. Concentrate.

468
01:00:28,000 --> 01:00:30,793
Just start at the beginning.

469
01:00:30,961 --> 01:00:33,421
Where are your parents?

470
01:00:34,048 --> 01:00:38,676
- Look, you have to try...
- Give it a rest, why don't you?

471
01:00:42,181 --> 01:00:46,059
- Total brain lock.
- Physically she's OK.

472
01:00:46,226 --> 01:00:49,228
Borderline malnutrition,
but no permanent damage.

473
01:00:49,396 --> 01:00:52,148
Come on. We're wasting our time.

474
01:01:01,367 --> 01:01:04,952
Try this. It's hot chocolate.

475
01:01:07,247 --> 01:01:09,290
There you go.

476
01:01:12,252 --> 01:01:14,295
That good, huh?

477
01:01:20,594 --> 01:01:27,600
I made a clean spot here. Now I've done it.
Guess I'll have to do the whole thing.

478
01:01:35,776 --> 01:01:40,738
Hard to believe there's
a little girl under all this.

479
01:01:40,906 --> 01:01:43,366
And a pretty one, too.

480
01:01:48,247 --> 01:01:50,832
You don't talk much, do you?

481
01:01:59,007 --> 01:02:03,136
- Smoking or non-smoking?
- Just tell me what you're scanning for.

482
01:02:03,303 --> 01:02:09,350
PDTs. Personal data transmitters.
Every colonist had one surgically implanted.

483
01:02:09,518 --> 01:02:14,856
If they're within 20 klicks
we'll read it out here. So far, zippo.

484
01:02:15,023 --> 01:02:20,361
I don't know how you managed to stay alive.
But you're one brave kid, Rebecca.

485
01:02:22,573 --> 01:02:24,282
Newt.

486
01:02:26,660 --> 01:02:31,497
- What'd you say?
- My name's Newt.

487
01:02:32,416 --> 01:02:36,544
Nobody calls me Rebecca
except my brother.

488
01:02:39,465 --> 01:02:41,340
I like that.

489
01:02:41,508 --> 01:02:44,510
I'm Ripley. It's nice to meet you.

490
01:02:47,639 --> 01:02:49,807
And who is this?

491
01:02:50,559 --> 01:02:54,103
- Casey.
- Hello, Casey.

492
01:02:55,522 --> 01:02:59,358
- What about your brother? What's his name?
- Timmy.

493
01:02:59,526 --> 01:03:04,363
Is Timmy around here too,
maybe hiding like you were?

494
01:03:07,701 --> 01:03:09,785
Any sisters?

495
01:03:13,207 --> 01:03:15,500
Mom and dad?

496
01:03:19,129 --> 01:03:21,380
Look at me. Where are they?

497
01:03:21,548 --> 01:03:24,592
They're dead, all right? Can I go now?

498
01:03:27,679 --> 01:03:29,847
I'm sorry.

499
01:03:30,641 --> 01:03:34,393
Don't you think
you'd be safer here with us?

500
01:03:36,855 --> 01:03:40,691
These people are here to protect you.
They're soldiers.

501
01:03:40,859 --> 01:03:43,694
It won't make any difference.

502
01:03:57,709 --> 01:04:00,002
Need anything else?

503
01:04:01,755 --> 01:04:04,715
Hello, Bishop.
Do you need anything else?

504
01:04:11,056 --> 01:04:15,768
- That's a nice pet you got there.
- Magnificent, isn't it?

505
01:04:17,479 --> 01:04:20,940
Stop your grinnin' and drop your linen.
Found 'em.

506
01:04:21,108 --> 01:04:25,653
- They alive?
- Unknown. But it looks like all of 'em.

507
01:04:26,530 --> 01:04:32,410
Over at the processing station.
Sub-level 3, under the main cooling towers.

508
01:04:33,745 --> 01:04:38,291
- Looks like a goddamn town meeting.
- Let's saddle up, Apone.

509
01:04:38,458 --> 01:04:40,751
Aye, sir.

510
01:04:40,919 --> 01:04:45,131
Let's go, people. They ain't payin' us
by the hour. Head 'em out.

511
01:04:45,299 --> 01:04:47,425
Frost, you're drivin'.

512
01:04:59,229 --> 01:05:02,148
Don't worry. It'll be OK.

513
01:05:43,565 --> 01:05:47,526
I want a straight V deployment.
Second team on left flank.

514
01:05:47,694 --> 01:05:50,488
Advance on axial 664.

515
01:05:50,656 --> 01:05:54,659
Tracker online.
Set the V-gain to filter RF ambient.

516
01:05:54,826 --> 01:05:59,705
Hudson, tracker online.
Left and right, little buddy.

517
01:05:59,873 --> 01:06:04,335
40 meters in, bearing 221 ,
there should be a stairwell.

518
01:06:04,503 --> 01:06:06,253
Check. Got it.

519
01:06:07,839 --> 01:06:10,341
You want sub-level 3.

520
01:06:11,927 --> 01:06:16,639
Let's go. Hudson, you got the point.
Hicks, watch our tails.

521
01:06:16,807 --> 01:06:19,809
Nice and easy. Check those corners.

522
01:06:25,732 --> 01:06:30,111
- Watch your spacing.
- You heard him. Don't bunch up. Stay loose.

523
01:06:30,278 --> 01:06:33,906
Your transmission's
showing a lot of break-up.

524
01:06:34,074 --> 01:06:38,828
- Probably interference from the structure.
- Use those lights.

525
01:06:39,871 --> 01:06:43,916
Next one down.
Then proceed on a 21 6.

526
01:06:44,084 --> 01:06:46,168
Roger. That's a 21 6.

527
01:06:48,797 --> 01:06:51,757
I'm not making that out too well.
What is it?

528
01:06:51,925 --> 01:06:55,136
You tell me, man. l only work here.

529
01:07:09,776 --> 01:07:11,652
What is that?

530
01:07:12,904 --> 01:07:14,864
I don't know.

531
01:07:15,907 --> 01:07:18,200
Proceed inside.

532
01:07:33,759 --> 01:07:36,761
Watch your fire
and check your targets.

533
01:07:36,928 --> 01:07:40,264
Remember we're looking for civvies.

534
01:07:49,316 --> 01:07:50,816
Easy.

535
01:07:50,984 --> 01:07:54,945
Tighten it up.
We're getting a little thin.

536
01:07:55,113 --> 01:07:57,364
Nice and easy.

537
01:07:59,701 --> 01:08:05,456
- Looks like some sort of secreted resin.
- But secreted from what?

538
01:08:05,624 --> 01:08:08,250
Nobody touch nothin'.

539
01:08:08,835 --> 01:08:11,295
Busy little creatures, huh?

540
01:08:12,047 --> 01:08:15,674
- Hot as hell in here.
- Yeah, but it's a dry heat.

541
01:08:15,842 --> 01:08:18,093
Knock it off.

542
01:08:25,936 --> 01:08:29,021
What do those pulse rifles fire?

543
01:08:29,189 --> 01:08:33,526
1 0mm explosive-tip caseless.
Standard light-armor-piercing round. Why?

544
01:08:33,693 --> 01:08:39,198
Look where your team is. They're right
under the primary heat exchangers.

545
01:08:39,366 --> 01:08:40,991
So?

546
01:08:41,159 --> 01:08:46,372
If they fire their weapons in there,
won't they rupture the cooling system?

547
01:08:46,540 --> 01:08:49,333
- She's absolutely right.
- So what?

548
01:08:49,876 --> 01:08:56,048
This whole station is basically
a big fusion reactor. Right?

549
01:08:56,216 --> 01:09:00,803
So you're talking about a thermonuclear
explosion and "Adiós, muchachos."

550
01:09:00,971 --> 01:09:03,556
Great. Wonderful.

551
01:09:04,432 --> 01:09:06,517
Shit.

552
01:09:08,812 --> 01:09:12,231
Look... Apone?

553
01:09:13,567 --> 01:09:20,781
We can't have any firing in there. I want
you to collect magazines from everybody.

554
01:09:20,949 --> 01:09:24,910
- Is he fucking crazy?
- What do we use, harsh language?

555
01:09:25,078 --> 01:09:27,913
Flame units only. I want rifles slung.

556
01:09:28,081 --> 01:09:30,916
Just do it, Sergeant. And no grenades.

557
01:09:32,711 --> 01:09:37,631
All right, sweethearts, you heard the man.
Come on, let's have 'em.

558
01:09:37,799 --> 01:09:40,718
Come on, Vasquez. Clear and lock.

559
01:09:43,763 --> 01:09:45,598
Damn.

560
01:09:45,765 --> 01:09:50,811
You too. Give it up, Ski.
Crowe, I want it now. Give it up.

561
01:09:50,979 --> 01:09:53,063
Right on, Vas.

562
01:09:54,649 --> 01:09:58,277
Let's go, Marine.
Frost, you got the duty. Open that bag.

563
01:09:58,445 --> 01:10:01,196
- Thanks a lot, sarge.
- Hicks, cover our ass.

564
01:10:01,364 --> 01:10:03,198
Head out, people.

565
01:10:05,619 --> 01:10:09,163
I like to keep this handy
for close encounters.

566
01:10:09,331 --> 01:10:10,831
I heard that.

567
01:10:20,175 --> 01:10:24,470
- Any movement?
- Nothing.

568
01:10:37,651 --> 01:10:39,777
Holy shit.

569
01:10:52,791 --> 01:10:55,000
Newt, go sit up front.

570
01:10:55,835 --> 01:10:58,170
Go on. Now.

571
01:11:26,491 --> 01:11:29,576
Steady, people.
Let's finish our sweep.

572
01:11:29,744 --> 01:11:34,540
We're still marines, and we got a job to do.
Keep it movin'.

573
01:11:35,542 --> 01:11:37,793
Easy.

574
01:12:08,408 --> 01:12:11,577
Top! Get over here. We got a live one.

575
01:12:11,745 --> 01:12:15,914
- You're gonna be all right.
- Please kill me.

576
01:12:16,082 --> 01:12:18,751
Just stay calm. We'll get you out of here.

577
01:12:18,918 --> 01:12:20,753
It's gonna be all right.

578
01:12:20,920 --> 01:12:23,130
- Oh, man.
- What is it, Dietrich?

579
01:12:23,298 --> 01:12:24,798
Convulsion!

580
01:12:25,967 --> 01:12:28,177
Dietrich, get back!

581
01:12:37,771 --> 01:12:39,646
- Flame-thrower.
- Kill it!

582
01:12:39,814 --> 01:12:42,441
Get back. Flame-thrower. Move!

583
01:13:13,306 --> 01:13:16,558
- Movement.
- What's the position?

584
01:13:17,310 --> 01:13:21,230
- I can't lock in.
- Talk to me.

585
01:13:22,148 --> 01:13:25,359
Multiple signals. They're closing.

586
01:13:27,320 --> 01:13:30,030
Go to infrared, people. Look sharp.

587
01:13:30,740 --> 01:13:35,536
- What's happening? We can't see anything.
- Pull your team out.

588
01:13:41,334 --> 01:13:44,419
I got readings in front and behind.

589
01:13:44,587 --> 01:13:48,507
- Where? I don't see shit.
- He's right. There's nothing back here.

590
01:13:48,675 --> 01:13:54,429
I'm tellin' ya.
There's somethin' moving, and it ain't us.

591
01:13:54,597 --> 01:14:00,185
Tracker's off-scale.
They're all around us. Jesus.

592
01:14:00,353 --> 01:14:04,064
Maybe they don't show up
on infrared at all.

593
01:14:19,831 --> 01:14:21,874
Come on!

594
01:14:28,798 --> 01:14:33,218
- Jesus Christ, what is going on?
- Wierzbowski and Crowe are down.

595
01:14:33,386 --> 01:14:36,221
Dietrich, Crowe, sound off.

596
01:14:49,736 --> 01:14:52,446
Let's rock!

597
01:14:55,241 --> 01:14:56,742
Who's firing?

598
01:14:59,078 --> 01:15:01,288
I ordered a hold fire.

599
01:15:01,456 --> 01:15:05,626
They're coming out
of the goddamn walls!

600
01:15:06,920 --> 01:15:10,756
Apone, I want you to lay down
a suppressing fire with...

601
01:15:10,924 --> 01:15:13,592
Hold your fire, goddammit.

602
01:15:13,760 --> 01:15:19,932
Apone, lay down a suppressing fire with
the incinerators and fall back by squads...

603
01:15:20,099 --> 01:15:23,352
Say again? All after "incinerators".

604
01:15:23,519 --> 01:15:28,607
I said lay down a suppressing fire
with the incinerators and fall back...

605
01:15:34,280 --> 01:15:36,490
Sarge!

606
01:15:36,658 --> 01:15:38,951
Talk to me. Apone?

607
01:15:39,118 --> 01:15:41,161
- Talk to me, Apone!
- He's gone!

608
01:15:43,039 --> 01:15:47,125
- Get them out of there, now!
- Shut up!

609
01:15:47,293 --> 01:15:50,295
- Whoever's left, get the hell out...
- Just shut up!

610
01:15:52,507 --> 01:15:55,300
Where's Apone?

611
01:15:55,468 --> 01:15:58,553
The sarge is gone.
Let's get the fuck outta here!

612
01:15:58,721 --> 01:16:01,181
Let's go, Marines.

613
01:16:05,144 --> 01:16:07,604
- Hudson, look out.
- Get it!

614
01:16:13,319 --> 01:16:15,779
- I told them to fall back.
- Fall back! Now!

615
01:16:15,947 --> 01:16:18,782
- I told them to fall back.
- They're cut off.

616
01:16:18,950 --> 01:16:22,119
Do something! Fuck!

617
01:16:23,037 --> 01:16:25,914
- Keep moving, baby.
- Hold on, Newt.

618
01:16:32,630 --> 01:16:34,965
What the hell are you doing?

619
01:16:41,139 --> 01:16:42,556
Turn it round!

620
01:16:45,935 --> 01:16:47,311
That's an order.

621
01:16:51,816 --> 01:16:55,193
- Turn this thing around.
- Get off me, damn it.

622
01:16:55,361 --> 01:16:58,071
You had your chance, Gorman.

623
01:17:09,709 --> 01:17:12,252
- Come on.
- Come on, Vas.

624
01:17:30,897 --> 01:17:32,898
Let's move it.

625
01:17:34,233 --> 01:17:35,901
Come on, let's go.

626
01:17:36,069 --> 01:17:39,404
It's blocked. We've got to go around.

627
01:17:39,572 --> 01:17:41,239
Open the door.

628
01:17:41,407 --> 01:17:44,242
Drake, we are leaving!

629
01:17:44,410 --> 01:17:46,495
Get them, Vas.

630
01:17:47,705 --> 01:17:50,082
Run for it.

631
01:17:51,250 --> 01:17:53,377
Shit.

632
01:17:57,799 --> 01:18:01,134
- Go.
- Drake, come on.

633
01:18:07,558 --> 01:18:09,726
Drake, come on.

634
01:18:18,611 --> 01:18:21,113
- Fire in the hold.
- He's gone.

635
01:18:21,280 --> 01:18:24,699
- No! Drake's out there!
- Put it out.

636
01:18:24,867 --> 01:18:28,120
- Drake's coming.
- He's gone.

637
01:18:28,287 --> 01:18:29,955
He's not!

638
01:18:32,125 --> 01:18:35,127
Forget him. He's gone.

639
01:18:39,132 --> 01:18:42,259
Get on the goddamn door!

640
01:18:44,470 --> 01:18:46,805
Eat this.

641
01:18:50,810 --> 01:18:52,811
Go!

642
01:19:55,708 --> 01:19:58,418
It's all right, we're clear.

643
01:19:58,586 --> 01:20:02,130
You've blown the transaxle.
You're just grinding metal.

644
01:20:02,298 --> 01:20:04,508
Come on, ease down.

645
01:20:22,568 --> 01:20:24,694
You OK?

646
01:20:27,865 --> 01:20:30,242
Get away from me!

647
01:20:30,409 --> 01:20:34,079
- Lieutenant.
- What happened to Gorman?

648
01:20:34,247 --> 01:20:37,290
I don't know. Maybe a concussion.

649
01:20:37,458 --> 01:20:39,543
- But he's alive.
- No, he's dead!

650
01:20:39,710 --> 01:20:45,423
- Wake up, Pendejo! Then l'm gonna kill you!
- Back off. Right now.

651
01:20:47,760 --> 01:20:51,137
Somebody get me a first-aid kit.

652
01:20:51,305 --> 01:20:58,270
Look. The sarge and Dietrich aren't dead.
Their signs were low, but they ain't dead.

653
01:20:58,437 --> 01:21:02,357
- Then we go back and get them.
- Fuck that. I ain't going back in there.

654
01:21:02,525 --> 01:21:05,694
You can't help them.

655
01:21:05,861 --> 01:21:11,908
You can't. Right now they're being
cocooned just like the others.

656
01:21:14,912 --> 01:21:19,124
Dear Lord Jesus, this ain't happenin'.

657
01:21:19,292 --> 01:21:22,127
This can't be happenin', man.

658
01:21:22,461 --> 01:21:26,089
All right.
We've got seven canisters of CN-20.

659
01:21:26,257 --> 01:21:29,467
I say we nerve-gas
the whole fuckin' nest.

660
01:21:29,635 --> 01:21:32,679
We don't know if it's gonna affect 'em.

661
01:21:32,847 --> 01:21:36,808
Let's just bug out and call it even.
Why are we talking about this?

662
01:21:36,976 --> 01:21:41,980
I say we take off
and nuke the entire site from orbit.

663
01:21:43,649 --> 01:21:45,817
It's the only way to be sure.

664
01:21:45,985 --> 01:21:48,528
- Fuckin' A.
- Hold on one second.

665
01:21:48,696 --> 01:21:52,824
This installation has a substantial
dollar value attached to it.

666
01:21:52,992 --> 01:21:55,160
They can bill me.

667
01:21:55,828 --> 01:22:01,625
Look, this is an emotional moment
for all of us. I know that.

668
01:22:01,792 --> 01:22:04,336
But let's not make snap judgments.

669
01:22:04,503 --> 01:22:07,422
This is clearly an important species,

670
01:22:07,590 --> 01:22:12,260
and I don't think we have the right
to arbitrarily exterminate them.

671
01:22:12,428 --> 01:22:14,679
- Wrong.
- Yeah. Watch us.

672
01:22:14,847 --> 01:22:17,223
Maybe you haven't kept up
on current events.

673
01:22:17,391 --> 01:22:20,518
We just got our asses kicked.

674
01:22:20,686 --> 01:22:23,438
I'm not blind to what's going on,

675
01:22:23,606 --> 01:22:27,192
but I cannot authorize
that kind of action. I'm sorry.

676
01:22:29,362 --> 01:22:34,282
I believe Corporal Hicks
has authority here.

677
01:22:36,035 --> 01:22:37,702
Corporal Hicks is...?

678
01:22:37,870 --> 01:22:41,039
This operation is under
military jurisdiction,

679
01:22:41,207 --> 01:22:44,793
and Hicks is next
in chain of command, right?

680
01:22:47,713 --> 01:22:50,090
That's right.

681
01:22:50,257 --> 01:22:54,886
Look, this is
a multi-million-dollar installation.

682
01:22:55,054 --> 01:22:58,765
He can't make that kind of decision.
He's just a grunt.

683
01:22:58,933 --> 01:23:01,267
- No offense.
- None taken.

684
01:23:01,435 --> 01:23:03,561
- Ferro, do you copy?
- Standing by.

685
01:23:03,729 --> 01:23:07,899
- Prep for dustoff. We need immediate evac.
- On our way.

686
01:23:08,067 --> 01:23:12,821
I say we take off, nuke the site from orbit.
It's the only way to be sure.

687
01:23:15,408 --> 01:23:17,075
Let's do it.

688
01:23:24,583 --> 01:23:27,711
Pick it up, Hudson.

689
01:23:33,217 --> 01:23:36,219
We'll set him down here.

690
01:23:41,767 --> 01:23:44,936
Move it, Spunkmeyer. We're rolling.

691
01:23:49,442 --> 01:23:53,319
- Hold on. There's something...
- Just get up here.

692
01:23:53,487 --> 01:23:55,905
I'm in. Ramp closing.

693
01:24:18,888 --> 01:24:20,972
Goddammit.

694
01:24:22,975 --> 01:24:24,893
Where the f...?

695
01:24:37,823 --> 01:24:39,908
Run.

696
01:25:20,574 --> 01:25:24,369
That's great. That's just fuckin' great.

697
01:25:24,537 --> 01:25:29,249
Now what the fuck do we do?
We're in some real pretty shit now!

698
01:25:29,416 --> 01:25:31,584
Are you finished?

699
01:25:34,547 --> 01:25:36,589
Are you all right?

700
01:25:41,512 --> 01:25:45,890
I guess we're not
gonna be leaving now, right?

701
01:25:46,058 --> 01:25:50,395
- I'm sorry.
- You don't have to be. It wasn't your fault.

702
01:25:50,563 --> 01:25:56,860
That's it. Game over, man.
What the fuck are we gonna do now?

703
01:25:57,027 --> 01:26:01,239
Maybe we could build a fire,
sing a couple of songs, huh?

704
01:26:01,407 --> 01:26:08,037
We'd better get back. It'll be dark soon,
and they mostly come at night. Mostly.

705
01:26:24,263 --> 01:26:26,598
That's everything, right?

706
01:26:26,765 --> 01:26:31,477
All right, this is everything
we can salvage out of the APC wreckage.

707
01:26:31,645 --> 01:26:35,189
We got four pulse rifles
with about 50 rounds each.

708
01:26:35,357 --> 01:26:37,150
That ain't so good.

709
01:26:37,318 --> 01:26:40,278
We got 1 5 of these M-40 grenades.

710
01:26:41,322 --> 01:26:44,490
Don't touch that. Dangerous, honey.

711
01:26:44,658 --> 01:26:49,662
- Is that the only flame-thrower?
- It's only half-full but it's functional.

712
01:26:49,830 --> 01:26:52,624
Got another one that's damaged.

713
01:26:54,752 --> 01:26:56,419
But the good news...

714
01:26:56,587 --> 01:26:59,464
We got four of these robot sentries,

715
01:26:59,632 --> 01:27:02,550
with display and scanners intact.

716
01:27:02,718 --> 01:27:05,803
They really kick ass.
They'll come in handy.

717
01:27:05,971 --> 01:27:09,432
How long after we're declared overdue
can we expect a rescue?

718
01:27:12,686 --> 01:27:14,437
1 7 days.

719
01:27:15,648 --> 01:27:22,111
1 7 days? I don't wanna rain on your parade,
but we're not gonna last 1 7 hours.

720
01:27:22,696 --> 01:27:27,075
Those things are gonna come in here
just like before...

721
01:27:29,078 --> 01:27:35,291
This little girl survived longer than that
with no weapons and no training. Right?

722
01:27:39,004 --> 01:27:42,757
- Why don't you put her in charge?
- You'd better deal with it.

723
01:27:42,925 --> 01:27:48,680
Just deal with it, because we need you
and I'm sick of your bullshit.

724
01:27:48,847 --> 01:27:53,184
I want you to get on a terminal
and call up a floor-plan file.

725
01:27:53,352 --> 01:27:59,023
Construction blueprints, anything that
shows the layout. Are you listening?

726
01:27:59,191 --> 01:28:04,028
I need to see air ducts,
electrical access tunnels, sub-basements,

727
01:28:04,196 --> 01:28:07,865
every possible way into this complex.

728
01:28:08,367 --> 01:28:13,871
- We don't have much time.
- OK. I'm on it.

729
01:28:15,249 --> 01:28:17,709
Just relax.

730
01:28:23,173 --> 01:28:28,011
I'll be in medlab.
Check on Gorman, continue my analysis.

731
01:28:28,178 --> 01:28:30,638
Fine. You do that.

732
01:28:37,771 --> 01:28:41,065
This service tunnel must be
how they move back and forth.

733
01:28:41,233 --> 01:28:48,156
That's right. It leads from the processing
station right into the sub-level here.

734
01:28:48,323 --> 01:28:52,827
Come down on that. OK, come over.
Go back...

735
01:28:52,995 --> 01:28:55,580
OK, punch that in right there.

736
01:29:00,544 --> 01:29:02,545
No. It's back here.

737
01:29:04,423 --> 01:29:07,175
There's a pressure door at this end.

738
01:29:07,342 --> 01:29:11,804
Couldn't we put a remote sentry unit
in the tunnel, then seal that door?

739
01:29:11,972 --> 01:29:15,141
Yeah, but we gotta figure
on them getting into the complex.

740
01:29:15,309 --> 01:29:20,605
That's right. So we repair the barricades
at these two intersections,

741
01:29:20,773 --> 01:29:26,944
and weld plate steel over these ducts
here, here and here.

742
01:29:27,112 --> 01:29:30,114
Then they can only come at us
from these two quarters.

743
01:29:30,282 --> 01:29:35,661
Right. Then we put the other sentry units
here and here. Right?

744
01:29:35,829 --> 01:29:38,498
- Right.
- Outstanding.

745
01:29:38,665 --> 01:29:41,584
Now all we need is a deck of cards.

746
01:29:42,920 --> 01:29:47,715
- OK, let's move like we got a purpose.
- Affirmative.

747
01:30:03,440 --> 01:30:06,651
Do your thing, baby.
Let's get the hell outta here.

748
01:30:06,819 --> 01:30:10,655
Hudson here. A and B sentries
are in place and keyed.

749
01:30:10,823 --> 01:30:12,949
Arming now.

750
01:30:13,534 --> 01:30:16,953
- Test it, Hudson.
- Fire in the hole!

751
01:30:20,499 --> 01:30:23,167
OK, let's get the hell outta here.

752
01:30:23,335 --> 01:30:26,504
We're sealing the tunnel. Come on, baby.

753
01:30:38,809 --> 01:30:41,060
For what it's worth.

754
01:30:42,563 --> 01:30:45,690
I want you to put this on.

755
01:30:46,400 --> 01:30:48,442
- What's it for?
- It's a locator.

756
01:30:48,610 --> 01:30:52,029
Then I can find you
anywhere in the complex on this.

757
01:30:53,866 --> 01:30:56,284
It's just a precaution.

758
01:30:56,451 --> 01:31:01,080
- Thanks.
- It doesn't mean we're engaged or anything.

759
01:31:01,248 --> 01:31:02,874
OK, what's next?

760
01:31:32,529 --> 01:31:34,572
Last stop.

761
01:31:38,744 --> 01:31:40,411
Get in.

762
01:31:40,579 --> 01:31:42,580
Scoot down.

763
01:31:43,957 --> 01:31:48,753
That's good.
Now, you have a nap. You're very tired.

764
01:31:48,921 --> 01:31:52,173
I don't want to sleep.
I have scary dreams.

765
01:31:54,635 --> 01:31:59,764
I bet Casey doesn't have scary dreams.
Let's take a look.

766
01:31:59,932 --> 01:32:02,099
Nothing bad in there.

767
01:32:02,267 --> 01:32:06,437
See? Maybe you could
just try to be like her.

768
01:32:06,605 --> 01:32:12,235
She doesn't have bad dreams
because she's just a piece of plastic.

769
01:32:12,402 --> 01:32:15,071
Right. I'm sorry.

770
01:32:22,496 --> 01:32:24,789
There.

771
01:32:24,957 --> 01:32:29,126
My mommy always said
there were no monsters, no real ones.

772
01:32:29,294 --> 01:32:34,382
- But there are.
- Yes, there are, aren't there?

773
01:32:36,593 --> 01:32:38,803
Why do they tell little kids that?

774
01:32:40,973 --> 01:32:43,474
Most of the time it's true.

775
01:32:43,642 --> 01:32:47,311
Did one of those things grow inside her?

776
01:32:47,479 --> 01:32:51,148
I don't know. That's the truth.

777
01:32:52,025 --> 01:32:55,820
Isn't that how babies come?
People babies?

778
01:32:55,988 --> 01:32:59,657
- They grow inside you.
- That's very different.

779
01:32:59,825 --> 01:33:04,829
- Did you ever have a baby?
- Yes, I did. I had a little girl.

780
01:33:04,997 --> 01:33:06,956
Where is she?

781
01:33:08,208 --> 01:33:12,336
- She's gone.
- You mean dead.

782
01:33:15,007 --> 01:33:16,549
Here.

783
01:33:18,010 --> 01:33:19,802
Take this.

784
01:33:20,554 --> 01:33:22,680
For luck.

785
01:33:25,809 --> 01:33:27,852
How's that?

786
01:33:30,230 --> 01:33:35,526
- Don't go. Please.
- I'm gonna be right in the next room.

787
01:33:35,694 --> 01:33:38,195
And you see that camera up there?

788
01:33:38,363 --> 01:33:44,535
I can see you through that camera
all the time to see if you're safe.

789
01:33:47,706 --> 01:33:53,711
I'm not gonna leave you.
I mean that. That's a promise.

790
01:33:53,879 --> 01:33:56,088
You promise?

791
01:33:57,215 --> 01:34:00,676
- I cross my heart.
- And hope to die.

792
01:34:02,220 --> 01:34:05,056
And hope to die.

793
01:34:18,278 --> 01:34:20,488
Now go to sleep.

794
01:34:20,655 --> 01:34:22,698
And don't dream.

795
01:34:26,912 --> 01:34:28,996
Sneak.

796
01:34:37,756 --> 01:34:41,801
The acid oxidises after the creature's death,
completely neutralizing.

797
01:34:41,968 --> 01:34:45,262
That's very interesting,
but it doesn't get us anywhere.

798
01:34:45,430 --> 01:34:50,267
I'm trying to figure out what we're
dealing with. Let's go through it again.

799
01:34:50,435 --> 01:34:56,941
They grab the colonists and immobilise them
to be hosts for more of these.

800
01:34:57,109 --> 01:35:00,778
Which means there would have
to be a lot of these parasites.

801
01:35:00,946 --> 01:35:04,949
- One for each colonist. Over 1 00 at least.
- That follows.

802
01:35:05,117 --> 01:35:09,286
But each of these things
comes from an egg, right?

803
01:35:12,040 --> 01:35:13,541
So who's laying these eggs?

804
01:35:14,793 --> 01:35:18,796
I'm not sure. It must be something
we haven't seen yet.

805
01:35:19,464 --> 01:35:23,217
- Maybe it's like an ant hive.
- Bees. Bees have hives.

806
01:35:23,385 --> 01:35:27,680
You know what I mean.
One female runs the whole show.

807
01:35:27,848 --> 01:35:30,933
- The queen.
- Yeah, the mama.

808
01:35:31,101 --> 01:35:35,146
- She's badass, man. I mean big.
- These things ain't ants.

809
01:35:35,313 --> 01:35:37,314
I know that.

810
01:35:37,482 --> 01:35:41,819
I want these specimens destroyed
when you're done. Is that clear?

811
01:35:42,988 --> 01:35:47,658
Mr. Burke wants them kept alive
for return to the company labs.

812
01:35:50,662 --> 01:35:52,997
He was very specific about it.

813
01:35:53,290 --> 01:35:57,376
Those two specimens are worth millions
to the bio-weapons division.

814
01:35:57,544 --> 01:36:01,046
If you're smart,
we can both come out of this heroes,

815
01:36:01,214 --> 01:36:03,674
and we will be set up for life.

816
01:36:05,135 --> 01:36:07,845
You're crazy, do you know that?

817
01:36:08,013 --> 01:36:12,183
You really think you can get a dangerous
organism past ICC quarantine?

818
01:36:12,350 --> 01:36:14,977
How can they impound it
if they don't know about it?

819
01:36:15,145 --> 01:36:18,189
But they will know about it. From me.

820
01:36:18,356 --> 01:36:22,526
Just like they'll know
you caused the deaths of 1 57 colonists.

821
01:36:22,694 --> 01:36:25,362
- Wait a second...
- You sent them to that ship.

822
01:36:25,530 --> 01:36:31,202
I just checked the colony log. Directive
dated 6/1 2/79, signed Burke, Carter J.

823
01:36:31,369 --> 01:36:34,205
You sent them out there
and didn't even warn them.

824
01:36:34,372 --> 01:36:36,749
Why didn't you warn them?

825
01:36:36,917 --> 01:36:40,127
What if that ship didn't even exist?
I didn't know.

826
01:36:40,295 --> 01:36:45,049
If I made a major security situation out of it,
administration steps in,

827
01:36:45,217 --> 01:36:47,551
and there's no exclusive rights
for anybody.

828
01:36:47,719 --> 01:36:53,557
So I made a decision, and it was wrong.
It was a bad call.

829
01:36:53,725 --> 01:36:59,438
Bad call? These people are dead!
Don't you have any idea what you've done?

830
01:36:59,606 --> 01:37:02,316
I'm gonna make sure
they nail you to the wall.

831
01:37:02,484 --> 01:37:09,031
You're not gonna sleaze your way
out of this one. Right to the wall.

832
01:37:12,035 --> 01:37:16,914
I expected more from you.
I thought you'd be smarter than this.

833
01:37:18,083 --> 01:37:20,668
I'm happy to disappoint you.

834
01:37:34,432 --> 01:37:38,978
- What's goin' on?
- They're coming. In the tunnel.

835
01:37:40,939 --> 01:37:45,943
Here we go. A and B gun
tracking and firing. Multiple targets.

836
01:37:51,783 --> 01:37:53,701
Look at those ammo counters go.

837
01:37:56,288 --> 01:37:58,455
B gun's down 50%0.

838
01:37:59,624 --> 01:38:03,127
Man, it's a shooting gallery down there.

839
01:38:05,797 --> 01:38:10,801
60 rounds left on B.
40... 20... 1 0.

840
01:38:10,969 --> 01:38:13,137
B gun's dry. 20 on A.

841
01:38:14,472 --> 01:38:16,932
1 0... 5...

842
01:38:20,812 --> 01:38:25,357
- That's it.
- Jesus. They're wall-to-wall in there.

843
01:38:29,487 --> 01:38:32,114
They're at the pressure door.

844
01:38:33,491 --> 01:38:36,827
- Listen to that.
- Bishop here.

845
01:38:36,995 --> 01:38:40,581
- I have some bad news.
- That's a switch.

846
01:38:43,001 --> 01:38:45,753
It's very pretty,
but what are we looking for?

847
01:38:45,920 --> 01:38:49,340
That's it. Emergency venting.

848
01:38:49,507 --> 01:38:54,136
That's beautiful, man. That beats it all.

849
01:38:54,304 --> 01:38:58,015
- How long till it blows?
- Four hours.

850
01:38:58,183 --> 01:39:03,896
With a blast radius of 30 kilometers,
equal to about 40 megatons.

851
01:39:04,064 --> 01:39:07,566
- We got problems.
- I don't fuckin' believe this.

852
01:39:07,734 --> 01:39:12,529
- Vasquez, close the shutters.
- Why can't we shut it down from here?

853
01:39:12,697 --> 01:39:16,950
I'm sorry. The crash caused too much
damage, and overload was inevitable.

854
01:39:17,118 --> 01:39:21,914
Oh, man. And I was gettin' short.
Four more weeks and out.

855
01:39:22,082 --> 01:39:25,542
- Now I'm gonna buy it on this rock.
- Give us a break.

856
01:39:25,710 --> 01:39:28,295
Four more weeks. Oh, man.

857
01:39:28,463 --> 01:39:31,799
We've got to get
the other dropship from the Sulaco.

858
01:39:31,966 --> 01:39:34,551
There must be some way
to bring it down on remote.

859
01:39:34,719 --> 01:39:38,222
How? The transmitter
was on the APC. It's wasted.

860
01:39:38,390 --> 01:39:41,975
I don't care how,
but we'd better think of something.

861
01:39:42,143 --> 01:39:44,395
We're fucked! We're doomed!

862
01:39:44,562 --> 01:39:47,314
Shut up!
What about the colony transmitters?

863
01:39:47,482 --> 01:39:50,734
- The uplink tower at the other end.
- No, I checked.

864
01:39:50,902 --> 01:39:55,239
The hard wiring between here and there
was damaged. We can't align the dish.

865
01:39:55,407 --> 01:39:57,950
Somebody has to go out there.

866
01:39:58,118 --> 01:40:01,412
Take a portable terminal
and patch in manually.

867
01:40:01,579 --> 01:40:05,916
Sure! With those things runnin' around?
You can count me out.

868
01:40:06,084 --> 01:40:08,919
- I guess we can count you out of everything.
- I'll go.

869
01:40:09,087 --> 01:40:11,004
- Why don't you go?
- I'll go.

870
01:40:11,172 --> 01:40:13,507
- What?
- I'll go.

871
01:40:13,675 --> 01:40:16,844
I'm the only one qualified
to remote-pilot the ship anyway.

872
01:40:17,011 --> 01:40:20,764
Right, Bishop should go. Good idea.

873
01:40:21,391 --> 01:40:27,020
Believe me, I'd prefer not to.
I may be synthetic, but I'm not stupid.

874
01:40:38,116 --> 01:40:39,616
How long?

875
01:40:39,784 --> 01:40:43,370
This conduit runs almost
to the uplink assembly. 1 80 meters.

876
01:40:43,538 --> 01:40:47,249
Say 40 minutes to crawl down there,

877
01:40:47,417 --> 01:40:51,462
an hour to patch in
and align the antenna,

878
01:40:51,629 --> 01:40:55,340
30 minutes to prep the ship,
and about 50 minutes flight time.

879
01:40:55,508 --> 01:40:58,010
It's gonna be close.

880
01:41:01,681 --> 01:41:04,183
- Good luck.
- See you soon.

881
01:41:05,977 --> 01:41:08,520
Watch your fingers.

882
01:41:25,705 --> 01:41:27,706
This is unbelievable.

883
01:41:27,874 --> 01:41:30,375
20 meters and closing.

884
01:41:30,543 --> 01:41:32,461
- 1 5.
- How many?

885
01:41:33,004 --> 01:41:35,130
Can't tell. Lots.

886
01:41:36,633 --> 01:41:38,926
D gun's down 50%.

887
01:41:41,971 --> 01:41:44,806
C gun's right behind it.

888
01:41:47,018 --> 01:41:50,229
It ain't stoppin' em.

889
01:41:50,522 --> 01:41:52,523
1 50 rounds on D.

890
01:41:52,690 --> 01:41:55,943
- Come on, baby.
- 1 00 rounds.

891
01:41:58,947 --> 01:42:00,489
Come on!

892
01:42:05,078 --> 01:42:07,746
D gun's down to 20.

893
01:42:08,665 --> 01:42:10,707
1 0.

894
01:42:11,876 --> 01:42:13,335
Damn it.

895
01:42:15,672 --> 01:42:17,881
Wait. They're retreating.

896
01:42:23,179 --> 01:42:25,889
The guns stopped them.

897
01:42:28,017 --> 01:42:29,601
You're right.

898
01:42:37,110 --> 01:42:41,363
- Next time they walk right up and knock.
- But they don't know that.

899
01:42:41,531 --> 01:42:46,785
They're probably looking for other ways
to get in. That'll take 'em a while.

900
01:42:46,953 --> 01:42:50,664
- Maybe we got 'em demoralised.
- Shut up.

901
01:42:50,832 --> 01:42:53,166
I want you two walking perimeter.

902
01:42:54,794 --> 01:42:56,920
Move.

903
01:43:03,636 --> 01:43:04,886
Listen.

904
01:43:05,930 --> 01:43:12,603
We're all in strung-out shape.
But stay frosty and alert.

905
01:43:13,605 --> 01:43:16,940
We can't afford to let
one of those bastards in here.

906
01:43:17,108 --> 01:43:18,817
All right.

907
01:43:29,829 --> 01:43:34,624
How long's it been since you got any sleep?
24 hours?

908
01:43:35,626 --> 01:43:41,631
I'm not gonna end up like those others.
You'll take care of it, won't you?

909
01:43:43,301 --> 01:43:47,804
If it comes to that, I'll do us both.

910
01:43:49,474 --> 01:43:53,977
Let's just make sure
it doesn't come to that. All right?

911
01:43:56,606 --> 01:44:01,318
I wanna introduce you
to a personal friend of mine.

912
01:44:01,486 --> 01:44:05,197
This is an M41-A pulse rifle, 1 0mm,

913
01:44:05,365 --> 01:44:09,826
with an over-and-under
30mm pump-action grenade launcher.

914
01:44:09,994 --> 01:44:12,204
Feel the weight.

915
01:44:18,169 --> 01:44:20,462
What do I do?

916
01:44:25,843 --> 01:44:28,637
Pull it in tight here.

917
01:44:29,680 --> 01:44:33,141
Lean into it. Now, it will kick.

918
01:44:33,851 --> 01:44:37,479
Right. When the counter reads zero here...

919
01:44:37,647 --> 01:44:40,357
- I press this up?
- That's right.

920
01:44:42,026 --> 01:44:45,570
And get another one in quick.
Slap it in hard.

921
01:44:45,738 --> 01:44:48,281
Now you're ready to rock'n'roll.

922
01:44:48,449 --> 01:44:51,368
- What's this?
- The grenade launcher.

923
01:44:51,536 --> 01:44:57,874
- I don't think you wanna mess with that.
- You started this. Show me everything.

924
01:44:58,042 --> 01:45:00,335
I can handle myself.

925
01:45:01,546 --> 01:45:03,422
I noticed.

926
01:45:13,724 --> 01:45:17,394
- How do you feel?
- All right, I guess.

927
01:45:17,562 --> 01:45:20,188
One hell of a hangover.

928
01:45:20,773 --> 01:45:25,402
- Look, I just want...
- Forget it. Excuse me.

929
01:46:21,626 --> 01:46:24,586
It's OK.

930
01:47:37,410 --> 01:47:39,244
- Wake up.
- Wha...?

931
01:47:39,412 --> 01:47:42,038
Be quiet. We're in trouble.

932
01:48:03,227 --> 01:48:05,103
Move!

933
01:48:36,844 --> 01:48:38,762
Help!

934
01:48:42,892 --> 01:48:47,937
Say again, Bishop. You've got it into
auto refuel mode, and it's sequencing right?

935
01:48:48,105 --> 01:48:52,275
- That's right.
- Good. Stay on it.

936
01:48:52,443 --> 01:48:56,988
Get back to me when
you've activated the launch cycle.

937
01:48:57,156 --> 01:49:00,450
- He's at the uplink tower.
- Terrific.

938
01:49:06,749 --> 01:49:08,291
Help us!

939
01:49:08,459 --> 01:49:10,460
Break the glass.

940
01:49:10,628 --> 01:49:12,545
Break it.

941
01:49:12,713 --> 01:49:14,798
I'll try.

942
01:49:35,820 --> 01:49:39,406
- I'm scared.
- Me too.

943
01:49:45,037 --> 01:49:46,913
Stay here.

944
01:49:59,510 --> 01:50:01,678
It's the medlab.

945
01:50:03,013 --> 01:50:07,183
- Meet me in the medlab. We got a fire.
- We're on our way.

946
01:50:10,062 --> 01:50:12,355
They're coming.

947
01:50:44,680 --> 01:50:46,723
Shoot it out!

948
01:50:51,854 --> 01:50:53,730
Jesus!

949
01:50:56,233 --> 01:50:58,568
Christ, kid, look out!

950
01:51:19,381 --> 01:51:22,592
Over there. Ready?

951
01:51:28,432 --> 01:51:32,393
All clear. Nailed the other one.
It's history, man.

952
01:51:33,813 --> 01:51:35,605
Jesus.

953
01:51:38,275 --> 01:51:40,610
It was Burke.

954
01:51:42,655 --> 01:51:45,615
I say we grease this rat-fuck
son of a bitch.

955
01:51:45,783 --> 01:51:49,160
It just doesn't make any goddamn sense.

956
01:51:51,622 --> 01:51:55,667
He figured he could get
an alien back through quarantine

957
01:51:55,835 --> 01:51:58,753
if one of us was impregnated...

958
01:51:59,755 --> 01:52:02,006
whatever you call it,

959
01:52:02,174 --> 01:52:04,926
and then frozen for the trip home.

960
01:52:05,678 --> 01:52:10,181
Nobody would know
about the embryos we were carrying.

961
01:52:10,349 --> 01:52:12,809
Me and Newt.

962
01:52:12,977 --> 01:52:14,853
We'd all know.

963
01:52:15,020 --> 01:52:22,193
He'd have to sabotage certain freezers
on the way home. Namely yours.

964
01:52:23,654 --> 01:52:27,490
Then he could jettison the bodies
and make up any story he liked.

965
01:52:27,658 --> 01:52:30,159
Fuck. He's dead.

966
01:52:30,703 --> 01:52:33,079
You're dog meat, pal.

967
01:52:34,123 --> 01:52:38,960
This is so nuts.
Listen to what you're saying.

968
01:52:39,128 --> 01:52:42,672
It's paranoid delusion. It's really sad.

969
01:52:45,009 --> 01:52:49,554
- It's pathetic.
- I don't know which species is worse.

970
01:52:49,722 --> 01:52:54,100
You don't see them fucking each other over
for a goddamn percentage.

971
01:52:54,268 --> 01:52:58,479
- All right, we waste him. No offense.
- No. He's gotta go back.

972
01:53:00,316 --> 01:53:04,611
- They cut the power.
- How could they cut it? They're animals.

973
01:53:04,778 --> 01:53:07,572
You two, check the corridors. Move!

974
01:53:07,740 --> 01:53:11,701
Gorman, watch Burke. Newt, stay close.

975
01:53:15,039 --> 01:53:18,207
- I'll go this side.
- You do that.

976
01:53:42,733 --> 01:53:44,901
- Anything?
- Somethin'.

977
01:53:46,403 --> 01:53:50,239
- It's inside the complex.
- You're just reading me.

978
01:53:51,742 --> 01:53:54,035
It ain't you.

979
01:53:55,079 --> 01:53:58,748
They're inside the perimeter.
They're in here.

980
01:53:58,916 --> 01:54:02,251
Stay cool. Vasquez?

981
01:54:08,801 --> 01:54:10,927
Hudson may be right.

982
01:54:11,428 --> 01:54:14,097
- Get back, both of you.
- The signal's weird.

983
01:54:15,391 --> 01:54:20,103
Must be interference or somethin'.
There's movement all over the place.

984
01:54:20,270 --> 01:54:22,772
Get back to Operations.

985
01:54:22,940 --> 01:54:24,941
It's game time.

986
01:54:27,569 --> 01:54:29,696
Seal the door.

987
01:54:29,863 --> 01:54:32,115
- Hurry.
- Come on.

988
01:54:32,282 --> 01:54:34,951
Come on, get back. Work fast.

989
01:54:39,790 --> 01:54:42,458
Cover your eyes. Don't look at the light.

990
01:54:42,626 --> 01:54:45,294
Movement. Signal's clean.

991
01:54:45,462 --> 01:54:47,463
Range 20 meters.

992
01:54:47,631 --> 01:54:51,801
- They've found a way in that we missed.
- We didn't miss anything.

993
01:54:51,969 --> 01:54:53,636
18.

994
01:54:54,638 --> 01:54:58,641
- 17 meters.
- Something under the floor, not in the plans.

995
01:54:58,809 --> 01:55:00,351
15 meters.

996
01:55:00,519 --> 01:55:03,980
- Definitely inside the barricades.
- Let's go.

997
01:55:05,607 --> 01:55:08,317
- 13 meters.
- That's right outside. Get back.

998
01:55:08,485 --> 01:55:12,113
- This is a big fucking signal.
- How you doing, Vasquez?

999
01:55:12,281 --> 01:55:14,449
Almost there.

1000
01:55:14,992 --> 01:55:16,659
That's it.

1001
01:55:17,619 --> 01:55:19,662
12 meters.

1002
01:55:19,830 --> 01:55:21,164
11 ...

1003
01:55:22,249 --> 01:55:24,417
- 10...
- Then they're right on us.

1004
01:55:24,585 --> 01:55:27,754
- Nine meters.
- Short controlled bursts.

1005
01:55:27,921 --> 01:55:29,297
Eight meters.

1006
01:55:32,051 --> 01:55:33,801
Seven.

1007
01:55:35,012 --> 01:55:37,847
- Six.
- Can't be. That's inside the room.

1008
01:55:38,015 --> 01:55:43,519
- It's readin' right. Look.
- Well, you're not reading it right.

1009
01:55:43,687 --> 01:55:46,522
Five meters, man. Four...

1010
01:55:46,690 --> 01:55:48,775
What the hell?

1011
01:55:51,487 --> 01:55:54,530
- Oh, my God...
- Give me the light.

1012
01:56:13,050 --> 01:56:15,510
Over there! Get 'em!

1013
01:56:17,179 --> 01:56:19,347
Come on.

1014
01:56:20,390 --> 01:56:22,809
Do something, Gorman.

1015
01:56:24,394 --> 01:56:27,438
Look out, there's more of 'em.

1016
01:56:27,606 --> 01:56:30,900
Get to Medical! Do it!

1017
01:56:31,401 --> 01:56:33,694
- Now!
- Look out, Hudson.

1018
01:56:39,201 --> 01:56:40,326
Now.

1019
01:56:46,333 --> 01:56:49,460
Open this door. Open it!

1020
01:56:52,422 --> 01:56:54,757
Fall back.

1021
01:56:59,638 --> 01:57:01,097
Die, motherfucker!

1022
01:57:06,270 --> 01:57:10,982
Motherfucker! Come and get it, baby!

1023
01:57:11,150 --> 01:57:15,236
I've got all day!
Come on, you bastards!

1024
01:57:15,404 --> 01:57:19,448
You too. You want some of this?
Fuck you!

1025
01:57:21,118 --> 01:57:22,994
Fuck you!

1026
01:57:35,382 --> 01:57:37,842
Come on, Hicks, go.

1027
01:57:38,010 --> 01:57:39,969
It's locked.

1028
01:57:57,529 --> 01:57:59,697
Got it. Let's go.

1029
01:57:59,865 --> 01:58:01,908
Go, go!

1030
01:58:03,285 --> 01:58:04,911
Move, Gorman.

1031
01:58:05,078 --> 01:58:07,496
Seal it.

1032
01:58:08,832 --> 01:58:11,626
Goddamn you, open this door.

1033
01:58:23,639 --> 01:58:25,223
- Get back.
- Hurry up.

1034
01:58:25,390 --> 01:58:28,017
- Gorman, get out of the way.
- This way.

1035
01:58:28,185 --> 01:58:29,852
What?

1036
01:58:30,854 --> 01:58:36,067
- Wait. Get behind me.
- Whatever you're gonna do, do it fast.

1037
01:58:38,237 --> 01:58:40,196
Come on, let's go.

1038
01:58:42,032 --> 01:58:43,366
Move.

1039
01:58:50,207 --> 01:58:53,876
- Which way to the landing field?
- This way.

1040
01:58:58,257 --> 01:59:00,383
Go right.

1041
01:59:03,720 --> 01:59:05,513
This way.

1042
01:59:14,773 --> 01:59:17,608
- Which way?
- Straight ahead and left.

1043
01:59:18,026 --> 01:59:21,237
Bishop, do you read me? Come in.

1044
01:59:21,405 --> 01:59:23,239
The ship is on its way.

1045
01:59:23,407 --> 01:59:26,367
ETA 1 6 minutes.

1046
01:59:26,535 --> 01:59:29,245
Good. Stand by there. We're on our way.

1047
01:59:40,632 --> 01:59:44,010
- Which way now?
- That way. No, wait. This way.

1048
01:59:44,177 --> 01:59:45,636
You sure?

1049
01:59:47,222 --> 01:59:48,764
Move!

1050
01:59:52,769 --> 01:59:54,895
It's just up here.

1051
01:59:55,897 --> 01:59:59,025
- We're almost there.
- Wait.

1052
02:00:28,930 --> 02:00:30,973
Go.

1053
02:00:47,657 --> 02:00:51,202
Up there. There's a shortcut
across the roof.

1054
02:01:02,798 --> 02:01:06,217
You always were an asshole, Gorman.

1055
02:01:27,906 --> 02:01:31,117
Hicks, get her. Hurry.

1056
02:01:36,039 --> 02:01:37,998
- Hold on.
- I'm slipping.

1057
02:01:38,166 --> 02:01:40,209
Don't let go.

1058
02:01:40,377 --> 02:01:42,378
- Hold on.
- Help!

1059
02:01:42,546 --> 02:01:44,255
Got ya.

1060
02:01:44,423 --> 02:01:46,132
I got ya.

1061
02:01:55,058 --> 02:01:58,060
We can find her with this.

1062
02:01:58,395 --> 02:02:02,565
Stay where you are. We're coming.

1063
02:02:20,375 --> 02:02:22,668
This way.

1064
02:02:23,712 --> 02:02:25,588
She's close.

1065
02:02:32,179 --> 02:02:34,430
Where are you? Can you hear me?

1066
02:02:36,391 --> 02:02:40,060
- I'm here.
- Where?

1067
02:02:45,066 --> 02:02:47,109
Are you OK?

1068
02:02:48,111 --> 02:02:50,946
- We need to cut it.
- Climb down, honey.

1069
02:02:51,114 --> 02:02:53,491
We've gotta cut through.

1070
02:03:03,293 --> 02:03:05,961
Don't move. Stay very still.

1071
02:03:08,131 --> 02:03:10,841
We're almost there. Hang in there.

1072
02:03:18,642 --> 02:03:21,352
- I know.
- Hurry. I mean it.

1073
02:03:35,992 --> 02:03:38,661
Newt, just stay still.

1074
02:03:43,458 --> 02:03:46,126
Almost there.

1075
02:04:03,853 --> 02:04:05,896
Let's go.

1076
02:04:06,064 --> 02:04:09,400
They don't kill you, they...

1077
02:04:09,568 --> 02:04:12,361
- She's alive!
- All right!

1078
02:04:12,529 --> 02:04:16,657
I believe you. She's alive.
We've gotta go. Now!

1079
02:04:49,733 --> 02:04:51,859
Get it off.

1080
02:05:02,245 --> 02:05:04,079
Here.

1081
02:05:08,418 --> 02:05:10,461
Go.

1082
02:05:12,756 --> 02:05:15,257
You can make it.

1083
02:05:39,074 --> 02:05:43,619
- Bishop, how much time?
- Plenty. 26 minutes.

1084
02:05:43,787 --> 02:05:47,122
- We're not leaving.
- We're not?

1085
02:07:12,333 --> 02:07:15,794
I don't wanna hear it.
She's alive. There's still time.

1086
02:07:15,962 --> 02:07:18,380
In 1 9 minutes,
this area's gonna be a vapor cloud.

1087
02:07:18,548 --> 02:07:20,966
- Don't let him leave.
- We ain't going anywhere.

1088
02:07:24,888 --> 02:07:27,473
- See you, Hicks.
- Dwayne.

1089
02:07:28,683 --> 02:07:30,350
It's Dwayne.

1090
02:07:32,228 --> 02:07:34,021
Ellen.

1091
02:07:34,856 --> 02:07:37,733
Don't be gone long, Ellen.

1092
02:07:45,283 --> 02:07:52,414
Attention. Emergency.
All personnel must evacuate immediately.

1093
02:07:52,582 --> 02:07:58,086
You have 1 5 minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.

1094
02:08:44,342 --> 02:08:47,052
Attention. Emergency.

1095
02:08:47,220 --> 02:08:51,431
All personnel must evacuate immediately.

1096
02:08:51,599 --> 02:08:56,979
You have 14 minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.

1097
02:12:55,885 --> 02:12:59,221
Grab on to me. Hold on.

1098
02:16:50,619 --> 02:16:52,287
Let's go.

1099
02:16:55,750 --> 02:16:57,667
Behind us.

1100
02:18:03,984 --> 02:18:08,988
You have four minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.

1101
02:18:24,755 --> 02:18:27,507
Come on, goddammit!

1102
02:18:33,556 --> 02:18:36,266
Hold on to me.

1103
02:19:31,071 --> 02:19:35,783
You have two minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.

1104
02:19:48,464 --> 02:19:51,299
Bishop, goddamn you!

1105
02:20:55,155 --> 02:20:57,198
Close your eyes, baby.

1106
02:20:59,535 --> 02:21:01,786
Look!

1107
02:21:08,794 --> 02:21:10,670
Come on.

1108
02:21:39,450 --> 02:21:41,701
Punch it.

1109
02:22:27,414 --> 02:22:29,457
We're OK.

1110
02:22:42,137 --> 02:22:44,305
We made it.

1111
02:22:44,473 --> 02:22:46,766
I knew you'd come.

1112
02:23:01,657 --> 02:23:07,161
He'll be all right. He's just out.
I had to give him another shot for the pain.

1113
02:23:07,329 --> 02:23:11,290
We need a stretcher
to carry him up to Medical.

1114
02:23:17,631 --> 02:23:21,551
Sorry if I scared you.
That platform was becoming too unstable.

1115
02:23:21,719 --> 02:23:26,305
I had to hope
things didn't get too rough to take you off.

1116
02:23:27,516 --> 02:23:30,184
- You did OK.
- I did?

1117
02:24:11,226 --> 02:24:13,186
Go. Move.

1118
02:24:15,898 --> 02:24:18,775
No, here!

1119
02:24:20,235 --> 02:24:21,611
Run.

1120
02:24:26,116 --> 02:24:27,742
Here.

1121
02:25:56,456 --> 02:25:58,749
Get away from her, you bitch!

1122
02:26:21,857 --> 02:26:24,400
Come on!

1123
02:29:55,737 --> 02:29:58,030
- Mommy.
- Oh, God...

1124
02:30:01,576 --> 02:30:04,829
Not bad for a human.

1125
02:30:52,085 --> 02:30:54,962
Are we gonna sleep all the way home?

1126
02:30:55,297 --> 02:30:57,965
- All the way home.
- Can I dream?

1127
02:31:00,135 --> 02:31:02,928
Yes, honey. I think we both can.

1128
02:31:11,062 --> 02:31:13,814
- Sleep tight.
- Affirmative.

1129
02:34:22,670 --> 02:34:23,670
[ENGLISH - US]

1130
02:34:29,469 --> 02:34:31,178
Come here.

1131
02:34:37,685 --> 02:34:39,686
It's all right.

1132
02:34:44,692 --> 02:34:46,568
It's over.

1133
02:34:55,620 --> 02:34:57,830
I don't understand this.

1134
02:34:57,997 --> 02:35:01,125
We have been here
for three and a half hours.

1135
02:35:01,292 --> 02:35:04,044
How many different ways
do you want me to tell the same story?

1136
02:35:17,851 --> 02:35:21,061
That could have been better.
Look, I think...

1137
02:35:21,229 --> 02:35:23,397
Van Leuwen?

1138
02:35:23,565 --> 02:35:26,900
Why don't you just check out LV-426?

1139
02:35:27,068 --> 02:35:30,737
I don't have to.
There have been people there over 20 years,

1140
02:35:30,905 --> 02:35:33,949
and they never mentioned
hostile organisms.

1141
02:35:34,117 --> 02:35:36,994
- What people?
- Terraformers.

1142
02:35:37,162 --> 02:35:42,749
Planet engineers. They set up big atmosphere
processors to make the air breathable.

1143
02:35:42,917 --> 02:35:47,212
Takes decades. It's what we call
a "shake'n'bake" colony.

1144
02:35:47,380 --> 02:35:50,924
How many colonists are there?

1145
02:35:51,593 --> 02:35:55,470
60, maybe 70 families. Do you mind?

1146
02:35:58,141 --> 02:36:00,267
Families.

1147
02:36:02,604 --> 02:36:04,396
Jesus.

1148
02:36:29,631 --> 02:36:34,176
- Lieutenant, am I right?
- We're trained to deal with these situations.

1149
02:36:34,344 --> 02:36:36,303
Then you don't need me.

1150
02:36:37,931 --> 02:36:40,390
We don't know
what's going on out there.

1151
02:36:40,558 --> 02:36:44,519
It may just be a downed transmitter, okay?
But if it's not,

1152
02:36:44,687 --> 02:36:48,732
I would like you there as an adviser,
and that's all.

1153
02:36:49,984 --> 02:36:52,736
I don't have time for this.
I've gotta get to work.

1154
02:36:54,322 --> 02:36:56,865
I heard you're working
in the cargo docks.

1155
02:36:57,033 --> 02:36:58,075
That's right.

1156
02:36:58,243 --> 02:37:00,911
- Running forklifts?
- So?

1157
02:37:01,079 --> 02:37:04,206
Nothing. It's great
that you're keeping busy.

1158
02:37:04,374 --> 02:37:09,836
And I know it's the only thing you
could get. There's nothing wrong with it.

1159
02:37:18,846 --> 02:37:21,181
And you, you little shithead,

1160
02:37:22,767 --> 02:37:25,644
you're staying here.

1161
02:38:48,895 --> 02:38:52,856
They ain't payin' us enough for this, man.

1162
02:38:53,024 --> 02:38:55,901
Not enough to have to
wake up to your face, Drake.

1163
02:38:56,069 --> 02:38:57,110
What?

1164
02:38:57,361 --> 02:39:01,531
That's better. Pan it around a bit.
Good.

1165
02:39:02,992 --> 02:39:04,576
All right, gear up.

1166
02:39:04,744 --> 02:39:10,207
Two minutes, people.
Somebody wake up Hicks.

1167
02:39:23,763 --> 02:39:27,849
- Coming around for a 709.
- Terminal guidance locked in.

1168
02:39:28,017 --> 02:39:30,102
Where's the damn beacon?

1169
02:39:30,269 --> 02:39:32,562
Oh, I see it.

1170
02:39:37,985 --> 02:39:41,238
- That's the atmosphere processor?
- That's it.

1171
02:39:41,405 --> 02:39:44,616
Remarkable piece of machinery.
Completely automated.

1172
02:39:44,784 --> 02:39:48,453
We manufacture those, by the way.

1173
02:39:57,463 --> 02:40:02,092
Ferro, take us in low
over the main colony complex.

1174
02:40:03,886 --> 02:40:08,014
Storm shutters are sealed.
There's no visible activity.

1175
02:40:08,182 --> 02:40:10,934
Hold at 40.

1176
02:40:34,584 --> 02:40:36,293
Hudson, try and get their CPU online.

1177
02:40:36,460 --> 02:40:37,586
Affirmative.

1178
02:40:37,753 --> 02:40:41,089
Hicks, meet me at the south lock.
We're coming in.

1179
02:40:41,549 --> 02:40:46,636
- He's comin' in. I feel safer already.
- Pendejo jerk-off.

1180
02:41:05,448 --> 02:41:07,782
That's everything, right?

1181
02:41:07,950 --> 02:41:12,662
All right, this is everything
we can salvage out of the APC wreckage.

1182
02:41:12,830 --> 02:41:16,374
We got four pulse rifles
with about 50 rounds each.

1183
02:41:16,542 --> 02:41:18,335
That ain't so good.

1184
02:41:18,502 --> 02:41:21,463
We got 1 5 of these M-40 grenades.

1185
02:41:22,506 --> 02:41:25,675
Don't touch that. Dangerous, honey.

1186
02:41:25,843 --> 02:41:30,847
- Is that the only flame-thrower?
- It's only half-full but it's functional.

1187
02:41:31,015 --> 02:41:33,808
Got another one that's damaged.

1188
02:41:35,436 --> 02:41:38,897
How long after we're declared overdue
can we expect a rescue?

1189
02:41:42,151 --> 02:41:43,902
1 7 days.

1190
02:41:45,112 --> 02:41:51,576
1 7 days? I don't wanna rain on your parade,
but we're not gonna last 1 7 hours.

1191
02:41:52,161 --> 02:41:56,539
Those things are gonna come in here
just like before...

1192
02:41:58,542 --> 02:42:04,756
This little girl survived longer than that
with no weapons and no training. Right?

1193
02:42:08,469 --> 02:42:12,222
- Why don't you put her in charge?
- You'd better deal with it.

1194
02:42:12,390 --> 02:42:18,144
Just deal with it, because we need you
and I'm sick of your bullshit.

1195
02:42:18,312 --> 02:42:22,649
I want you to get on a terminal
and call up a floor-plan file.

1196
02:42:22,817 --> 02:42:28,488
Construction blueprints, anything that
shows the layout. Are you listening?

1197
02:42:28,656 --> 02:42:33,493
I need to see air ducts,
electrical access tunnels, sub-basements,

1198
02:42:33,661 --> 02:42:37,330
every possible way into this complex.

1199
02:42:37,832 --> 02:42:43,336
- We don't have much time.
- OK. I'm on it.

1200
02:42:44,714 --> 02:42:47,173
Just relax.

1201
02:42:52,638 --> 02:42:57,475
I'll be in medlab.
Check on Gorman, continue my analysis.

1202
02:42:57,643 --> 02:43:00,103
Fine. You do that.

1203
02:43:07,236 --> 02:43:10,530
This service tunnel must be
how they move back and forth.

1204
02:43:10,698 --> 02:43:17,620
That's right. It leads from the processing
station right into the sub-level here.

1205
02:43:17,788 --> 02:43:22,292
Come down on that. OK, come over.
Go back...

1206
02:43:22,460 --> 02:43:25,045
OK, punch that in right there.

1207
02:43:30,009 --> 02:43:32,010
No. It's back here.

1208
02:43:33,888 --> 02:43:36,222
There's a pressure door at this end.

1209
02:43:36,390 --> 02:43:39,934
We could weld it shut.
That should hold them for a while.

1210
02:43:40,102 --> 02:43:42,395
But we gotta figure
on them getting into the complex.

1211
02:43:42,563 --> 02:43:47,817
That's right. So we repair the barricades
at these two intersections,

1212
02:43:47,985 --> 02:43:53,865
and weld plate steel over these ducts
here, here and here.

1213
02:43:54,033 --> 02:43:56,576
That should seal off Medlab and Operations.

1214
02:43:56,786 --> 02:43:58,661
Outstanding.

1215
02:43:58,829 --> 02:44:00,580
Now all we need is a deck of cards.

1216
02:44:03,000 --> 02:44:07,796
- OK, let's move like we got a purpose.
- Affirmative.

1217
02:44:10,091 --> 02:44:13,259
We're sealing the tunnel. Come on, baby.

1218
02:44:25,940 --> 02:44:28,191
For what it's worth.

1219
02:44:29,693 --> 02:44:32,779
I want you to put this on.

1220
02:44:33,531 --> 02:44:35,573
- What's it for?
- It's a locator.

1221
02:44:35,741 --> 02:44:39,160
Then I can find you
anywhere in the complex on this.

1222
02:44:40,955 --> 02:44:43,414
It's just a precaution.

1223
02:44:43,582 --> 02:44:48,211
- Thanks.
- It doesn't mean we're engaged or anything.

1224
02:44:48,379 --> 02:44:50,004
OK, what's next?

1225
02:45:07,398 --> 02:45:09,482
Last stop.

1226
02:45:13,612 --> 02:45:15,280
Get in.

1227
02:45:15,447 --> 02:45:17,490
Scoot down.

1228
02:45:18,826 --> 02:45:23,621
That's good.
Now, you have a nap. You're very tired.

1229
02:45:23,789 --> 02:45:27,041
I don't want to sleep.
I have scary dreams.

1230
02:45:29,503 --> 02:45:34,674
I bet Casey doesn't have scary dreams.
Let's take a look.

1231
02:45:34,842 --> 02:45:37,010
Nothing bad in there.

1232
02:45:37,178 --> 02:45:41,347
See? Maybe you could
just try to be like her.

1233
02:45:41,515 --> 02:45:47,103
She doesn't have bad dreams
because she's just a piece of plastic.

1234
02:45:47,271 --> 02:45:49,939
Right. I'm sorry.

1235
02:45:57,364 --> 02:45:59,699
There.

1236
02:45:59,867 --> 02:46:04,037
My mommy always said
there were no monsters, no real ones.

1237
02:46:04,205 --> 02:46:09,250
- But there are.
- Yes, there are, aren't there?

1238
02:46:11,462 --> 02:46:13,713
Why do they tell little kids that?

1239
02:46:15,883 --> 02:46:18,384
Most of the time it's true.

1240
02:46:21,138 --> 02:46:22,722
Here.

1241
02:46:23,599 --> 02:46:27,685
The acid oxidizes after the creature's death,
completely neutralizing.

1242
02:46:27,853 --> 02:46:31,147
That's very interesting,
but it doesn't get us anywhere.

1243
02:46:31,315 --> 02:46:36,152
I'm trying to figure out what we're
dealing with. Let's go through it again.

1244
02:46:36,320 --> 02:46:42,784
They grab the colonists and immobilize them
to be hosts for more of these.

1245
02:46:42,952 --> 02:46:46,663
Which means there would have
to be a lot of these parasites.

1246
02:46:46,830 --> 02:46:50,833
- One for each colonist. Over 1 00 at least.
- That follows.

1247
02:46:51,001 --> 02:46:55,129
But each of these things
comes from an egg, right?

1248
02:46:57,883 --> 02:46:59,384
So who's laying these eggs?

1249
02:47:00,636 --> 02:47:04,681
I'm not sure. It must be something
we haven't seen yet.

1250
02:47:09,353 --> 02:47:13,690
I want these specimens destroyed
when you're done. Is that clear?

1251
02:47:14,858 --> 02:47:19,529
Mr. Burke wants them kept alive
for return to the company labs.

1252
02:47:22,574 --> 02:47:24,909
He was very specific about it.

1253
02:47:27,329 --> 02:47:32,208
I expected more from you.
I thought you'd be smarter than this.

1254
02:47:33,419 --> 02:47:35,962
I'm happy to disappoint you.

1255
02:47:49,727 --> 02:47:52,061
I want you two walking perimeter.

1256
02:47:52,730 --> 02:47:53,980
Listen.

1257
02:47:55,065 --> 02:48:01,738
We're all in strung-out shape.
But stay frosty and alert.

1258
02:48:02,740 --> 02:48:06,075
We can't afford to let
one of those bastards in here.

1259
02:48:06,243 --> 02:48:07,910
All right.

1260
02:48:46,825 --> 02:48:50,286
I don't wanna hear it.
She's alive. There's still time.

1261
02:48:50,454 --> 02:48:52,830
In 1 9 minutes,
this area's gonna be a vapor cloud.

1262
02:48:52,998 --> 02:48:55,458
- Don't let him leave.
- We ain't going anywhere.

1263
02:49:00,005 --> 02:49:07,136
Attention. Emergency.
All personnel must evacuate immediately.

1264
02:49:07,304 --> 02:49:12,850
You have 1 5 minutes
to reach minimum safe distance.

1265
02:49:16,396 --> 02:49:19,148
- Sleep tight.
- Affirmative.

1266
02:52:28,130 --> 02:52:29,130
[ENGLISH - US]
